{
	"description": "Beyond N1! Readings outside of jouyou",
	"deck": [
	{ "question": "たん瘤", "answers": [ "たんこぶ" ], "comment": "bump; lump; protuberance; swelling" },
	{ "question": "一揆", "answers": [ "いっき" ], "comment": "uprising (esp. in Japan since middle ages, e.g. peasant uprising); revolt; insurrection; putsch; riot" },
	{ "question": "一矢", "answers": [ "いっし" ], "comment": "an arrow; (a) retort" },
	{ "question": "一縷", "answers": [ "いちる" ], "comment": "a thread; a ray or sliver (of hope)" },
	{ "question": "丁稚", "answers": [ "でっち" ], "comment": "apprentice; shop boy" },
	{ "question": "上戸", "answers": [ "じょうご" ], "comment": "heavy drinker; drinker's habits" },
	{ "question": "上背", "answers": [ "うわぜい" ], "comment": "stature; height" },
	{ "question": "下戸", "answers": [ "げこ" ], "comment": "someone who can't drink; non-drinker; temperate man" },
	{ "question": "下賤", "answers": [ "げせん" ], "comment": "low birth; humble origin\nlowly; base; vulgar; coarse" },
	{ "question": "不束者", "answers": [ "ふつつかもの" ], "comment": "incompetent person; ignoramus" },
	{ "question": "与する", "answers": [ "くみする" ], "comment": "to take part in; to be implicated in; to side with; to support" },
	{ "question": "与る", "answers": [ "あずかる" ], "comment": "to participate in; to take part in\nto receive; to enjoy; to be given" },
	{ "question": "乖離", "answers": [ "かいり" ], "comment": "divergence; alienation; deviation; estrangement; separation; detachment" },
	{ "question": "也", "answers": [ "なり" ], "comment": "to be (an affirmation)\nto be (location)\nsum of money (used to express an exact sum on a receipt, envelope, certificate, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "予め", "answers": [ "あらかじめ" ], "comment": "beforehand; in advance; previously" },
	{ "question": "云々", "answers": [ "うんぬん" ], "comment": "and so on; and so forth; et cetera; and such; and the like\ncomment; criticism" },
	{ "question": "些か", "answers": [ "いささか" ], "comment": "a little; a bit; somewhat; slightly; rather" },
	{ "question": "人伝に", "answers": [ "ひとづてに" ] }, "comment": "hearsay; to leave a message with someone; (to send anything) by another's hand" },
	{ "question": "人間業", "answers": [ "にんげんわざ" ], "comment": "the work of man" },
	{ "question": "仄暗い", "answers": [ "ほのぐらい" ], "comment": "gloomy; obscure" },
	{ "question": "仇", "answers": [ "あだ", "かたき" ], "comment": "foe; enemy; rival\nresentment; enmity; grudge\nharm; injury\nrival; opponent; adversary; competitor; enemy (esp. one with which there is longstanding enmity); foe\nrevenge\nspouse" },
	{ "question": "今宵", "answers": [ "こよい" ], "comment": "this evening; tonight" },
	{ "question": "今昔", "answers": [ "こんじゃく" ], "comment": "past and present" },
	{ "question": "仕る", "answers": [ "つかまつる" ], "comment": "to serve; to do" },
	{ "question": "仰け反る", "answers": [ "のけぞる" ], "comment": "to bend (backward); to throw (the head) back\nto be taken aback" },
	{ "question": "仰せ付かる", "answers": [ "おおせつかる" ], "comment": "to receive a command; to be appointed; to be ordered" },
	{ "question": "仲人", "answers": [ "なこうど" ], "comment": "matchmaker\ngo-between; intermediary; middleman; mediator; intercessor\ngo-between; matchmaker" },
	{ "question": "伊達", "answers": [ "だて" ], "comment": "elegance; dandyism; sophistication; having style\naffectation; showing off; putting on an air; appearances; doing something just for show" },
	{ "question": "伝播", "answers": [ "でんぱ" ], "comment": "transmission; propagation; spread; circulation; diffusion; dissemination" },
	{ "question": "何卒", "answers": [ "なにとぞ" ], "comment": "please; kindly; I beg of you; if it pleases you\nby all means; without fail" },
	{ "question": "何某", "answers": [ "なにがし", "なにぼう" ], "comment": "certain amount; some\ncertain person; Mr So-and-so; a certain ...\nI; me" },
	{ "question": "併呑", "answers": [ "へいどん" ], "comment": "annexation; merger; swallowing up" },
	{ "question": "侍る", "answers": [ "はべる" ], "comment": "to wait upon; to serve" },
	{ "question": "依嘱", "answers": [ "いしょく" ], "comment": "entrusting (with)" },
	{ "question": "俄", "answers": [ "にわか" ], "comment": "sudden; abrupt; unexpected; improvised; hasty; offhand\nimpromptu skit" },
	{ "question": "俊敏", "answers": [ "しゅんびん" ], "comment": "quick-witted and agile; keen and nimble" },
	{ "question": "信憑", "answers": [ "しんぴょう" ], "comment": "trust; credit; credence" },
	{ "question": "信憑性", "answers": [ "しんぴょうせい" ], "comment": "authenticity; credibility" },
	{ "question": "修祓", "answers": [ "しゅばつ", "しゅうばつ", "しゅうふつ" ], "comment": "purification rite (esp. one held prior to a Shinto event)" },
	{ "question": "俯く", "answers": [ "うつむく" ], "comment": "to hang one's head; to look down; to cast one's eyes downward" },
	{ "question": "俯瞰", "answers": [ "ふかん" ], "comment": "overlooking; looking down at; having an overhead view; having a bird's-eye view; having a high-angle view" },
	{ "question": "倦む", "answers": [ "うむ", "あぐむ" ], "comment": "to get tired of (doing); to lose interest in" },
	{ "question": "倦怠", "answers": [ "けんたい" ], "comment": "languor; fatigue; weariness; boredom" },
	{ "question": "偏に", "answers": [ "ひとえに" ], "comment": "earnestly; humbly; solely" },
	{ "question": "偶に", "answers": [ "たまに" ], "comment": "occasionally; once in a while" },
	{ "question": "傀儡", "answers": [ "かいらい", "くぐつ" ], "comment": "puppet; dummy\nprostitute" },
	{ "question": "傅く", "answers": [ "かしずく", "かしづく" ], "comment": "to wait upon; to serve" },
	{ "question": "傍目", "answers": [ "はため", "おかめ" ], "comment": "looking on from the side; looking on by an outsider\noutsider's perspective; as seen by an observer" },
	{ "question": "傭兵", "answers": [ "ようへい" ], "comment": "mercenary (soldier)" },
	{ "question": "傲慢", "answers": [ "ごうまん" ], "comment": "haughty; arrogant; insolent; proud; overbearing" },
	{ "question": "僥倖", "answers": [ "ぎょうこう" ], "comment": "fortuitous; luck; windfall; godsend; good fortune" },
	{ "question": "僭越", "answers": [ "せんえつ" ], "comment": "presumptuous; arrogant; audacious; forward; insolent" },
	{ "question": "儂", "answers": [ "わし" ], "comment": "I; me (used by elderly males)" },
	{ "question": "億劫", "answers": [ "おっくう" ], "comment": "troublesome; annoying" },
	{ "question": "儚い", "answers": [ "はかない" ], "comment": "fleeting; transient; short-lived; momentary; ephemeral; fickle; vain\nempty (dream, etc.); mere (hope); faint (possibility)" },
	{ "question": "儲ける", "answers": [ "もうける" ], "comment": "to profit; to get; to earn; to gain\nto have (bear, beget) a child\nto have a stroke of luck" },
	{ "question": "兎", "answers": [ "うさぎ" ], "comment": "rabbit; hare; coney; cony; lagomorph (esp. leporids)" },
	{ "question": "脱兎", "answers": [ "だっと" ], "comment": "dashing away; bounding away; (with) lightning speed\nstartled hare" },
	{ "question": "内腿", "answers": [ "うちもも" ], "comment": "inner thigh\n(walking) pigeon-toed; one's toes turned inward\nuchimata (judo); throwing an opponent by putting one's leg between their legs" },
	{ "question": "内謁", "answers": [ "ないえつ" ], "comment": "private audience" },
	{ "question": "円錐", "answers": [ "えんすい", "まるぎり" ], "comment": "cone\nround gimlet" },
	{ "question": "冒涜", "answers": [ "ぼうとく" ], "comment": "blasphemy; curse; profanity; sacrilege; desecration" },
	{ "question": "冥利", "answers": [ "みょうり" ], "comment": "providence; luck; favor; favour; advantage" },
	{ "question": "冪乗", "answers": [ "べきじょう" ], "comment": "exponentiation; power" },
	{ "question": "冴える", "answers": [ "さえる" ], "comment": "to be clear (of a sight, sound, colour, etc.); to be bright; to be vivid; to be crisp\nto be clear-headed; to be alert; to be on the ball; to be wide awake\nto look upbeat; to be perky; to be cheerful\nto master (a skill); to excel at; to cleanly execute\nto be satisfying\nto become frigid; to become intensely cold" },
	{ "question": "凌ぐ", "answers": [ "しのぐ" ], "comment": "to endure; to keep out (e.g. rain); to stave off (e.g. starvation)\nto pull through; to get over; to survive\nto surpass; to outdo; to excel; to eclipse; to defy; to slight" },
	{ "question": "凌辱", "answers": [ "りょうじょく" ], "comment": "insult; affront; disgrace; indignity\nsexual assault; rape" },
	{ "question": "凌駕", "answers": [ "りょうが" ], "comment": "excelling; surpassing; outdoing" },
	{ "question": "凛々しい", "answers": [ "りりしい" ], "comment": "gallant; brave; imposing; awe-inspiring; severe; biting; chivalrous; manly; dignified" },
	{ "question": "几帳面", "answers": [ "きちょうめん" ], "comment": "methodical; punctual; steady" },
	{ "question": "凱旋", "answers": [ "がいせん" ], "comment": "triumphal return" },
	{ "question": "出納", "answers": [ "すいとう" ], "comment": "receipts and expenditure (disbursements)" },
	{ "question": "刃傷", "answers": [ "にんじょう" ], "comment": "bloodshed" },
	{ "question": "分水嶺", "answers": [ "ぶんすいれい" ], "comment": "watershed; divide" },
	{ "question": "初陣", "answers": [ "ういじん" ], "comment": "first campaign; one's first battle" },
	{ "question": "刺繍", "answers": [ "ししゅう" ], "comment": "embroidery" },
	{ "question": "剃る", "answers": [ "そる", "する" ], "comment": "to shave" },
	{ "question": "則る", "answers": [ "のっとる" ], "comment": "to conform to; to be in accordance with; to follow (rule, tradition, example, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "剣呑", "answers": [ "けんのん" ], "comment": "risky; dangerous; insecure" },
	{ "question": "剣戟", "answers": [ "けんげき" ], "comment": "weapons; arms\nfighting with swords; sword fight" },
	{ "question": "剪定", "answers": [ "せんてい" ], "comment": "pruning" },
	{ "question": "剰え", "answers": [ "あまつさえ" ], "comment": "besides (usu. negative nuance); moreover; in addition" },
	{ "question": "剽悍", "answers": [ "ひょうかん" ], "comment": "fierceness; daring" },
	{ "question": "力む", "answers": [ "りきむ" ], "comment": "to strain; to bear up; to exert one's strength\nto swagger; to bluff; to boast" },
	{ "question": "労う", "answers": [ "ねぎらう" ], "comment": "to thank for; to reward for" },
	{ "question": "労る", "answers": [ "いたわる" ], "comment": "to pity; to sympathize with; to sympathise with; to treat with sympathy; to console; to be kind to; to appreciate\nto tend to (e.g. an injury); to care for; to nurse; to soothe" },
	{ "question": "動じる", "answers": [ "どうじる" ], "comment": "to be perturbed; to be agitated" },
	{ "question": "勝鬨", "answers": [ "かちどき" ], "comment": "shout of victory; cry of triumph" },
	{ "question": "勢揃い", "answers": [ "せいぞろい" ], "comment": "array; muster; line-up; full force" },
	{ "question": "勿論", "answers": [ "もちろん" ], "comment": "of course; certainly; naturally" },
	{ "question": "匍匐", "answers": [ "ほふく" ], "comment": "creeping; crawling; sneaking" },
	{ "question": "化膿", "answers": [ "かのう" ], "comment": "suppuration; festering; coming to head" },
	{ "question": "匙", "answers": [ "さじ", "しゃじ" ], "comment": "spoon" },
	{ "question": "卑怯", "answers": [ "ひきょう" ], "comment": "cowardice; meanness; unfairness" },
	{ "question": "博打", "answers": [ "ばくち" ], "comment": "gambling" },
	{ "question": "即ち", "answers": [ "すなわち" ], "comment": "that is; namely; i.e." },
	{ "question": "却って", "answers": [ "かえって" ], "comment": "on the contrary; rather; all the more; instead" },
	{ "question": "卿", "answers": [ "きょう", "けい" ], "comment": "lord; sir\nstate minister (i.e. under the ritsuryo system)\nyou (in reference to someone of lower status)" },
	{ "question": "厠", "answers": [ "かわや" ], "comment": "privy; toilet" },
	{ "question": "厩", "answers": [ "うまや" ], "comment": "stable; barn" },
	{ "question": "厩舎", "answers": [ "きゅうしゃ" ], "comment": "barn; stable" },
	{ "question": "厭う", "answers": [ "いとう" ], "comment": "to be loath to; to balk at (doing); to grudge (doing); to spare (oneself); to be weary of; to shun; to dislike (an activity, an environment); to hate (an activity)\nto take (good) care of" },
	{ "question": "厭世", "answers": [ "えんせい" ], "comment": "pessimism; weariness with life" },
	{ "question": "厳めしい", "answers": [ "いかめしい" ], "comment": "stern; austere; grave; dignified; formidable; solemn; majestic\nsevere; strict; rigid; unsparing; relentless" },
	{ "question": "友誼", "answers": [ "ゆうぎ" ], "comment": "friendship; friendly relations; fellowship" },
	{ "question": "反芻", "answers": [ "はんすう" ], "comment": "rumination; regurgitation; chewing the cud\nturning over in one's mind; thinking over something; pondering; musing; rumination (about a subject)" },
	{ "question": "収斂", "answers": [ "しゅうれん" ], "comment": "astringency\nextraction (of taxes)\nconvergence; contraction" },
	{ "question": "叢雲", "answers": [ "むらくも" ], "comment": "gathering clouds; group of clouds" },
	{ "question": "口火", "answers": [ "くちび" ], "comment": "fuse; pilot light\ncause (of a war, argument, revolt, etc.); origin; trigger" },
	{ "question": "口調", "answers": [ "くちょう" ], "comment": "tone (e.g. of voice, etc.); (verbal) expression" },
	{ "question": "叩く", "answers": [ "たたく", "はたく" ], "comment": "to strike; to clap; to knock; to beat; to tap; to pat\nto play drums\nto abuse; to flame (e.g. on the Internet); to insult\nto consult; to sound out\nto brag; to talk big\nto call; to invoke (e.g. a function)\nto dust; to remove dust\nto slap; to hit (with the palm)\nto use up money" },
	{ "question": "可憐", "answers": [ "かれん" ], "comment": "sweet (e.g. young girls, flowers blooming); touchingly lovely; cute\npitiful; pitiable" },
	{ "question": "台詞", "answers": [ "せりふ" ], "comment": "speech; words; one's lines; remarks" },
	{ "question": "叶う", "answers": [ "かなう" ], "comment": "to come true (wish)\nto be suited\nto match (implies competition); to rival; to bear (e.g. I can't bear the heat)" },
	{ "question": "吃る", "answers": [ "どもる" ], "comment": "to stammer; to stutter" },
	{ "question": "吃逆", "answers": [ "しゃっくり" ], "comment": "hiccough; hiccup" },
	{ "question": "吃驚", "answers": [ "びっくり", "きっきょう" ], "comment": "to be surprised; to be amazed; to be frightened; to be astonished; to get startled; to jump\nsurprise (e.g. surprise party)\nsurprise" },
	{ "question": "吊り上げる", "answers": [ "つりあげる" ], "comment": "to raise; to lift; to hang up; to suspend\nto raise prices (artificially, deliberately)" },
	{ "question": "吊るす", "answers": [ "つるす" ], "comment": "to hang; to hang up" },
	{ "question": "同棲", "answers": [ "どうせい" ], "comment": "cohabitation (usu. of a romantically involved couple); living together" },
	{ "question": "同衾", "answers": [ "どうきん" ], "comment": "sleeping together; sleeping with; sharing a bed" },
	{ "question": "后", "answers": [ "きさき" ], "comment": "empress; queen\nafter" },
	{ "question": "吝か", "answers": [ "やぶさか" ], "comment": "reluctant; hesitant" },
	{ "question": "吝嗇", "answers": [ "りんしょく", "けち" ], "comment": "stinginess; miser; miserliness; selfishness" },
	{ "question": "吠える", "answers": [ "ほえる" ], "comment": "to bark; to bay; to howl; to bellow; to roar; to cry" },
	{ "question": "吶喊", "answers": [ "とっかん" ], "comment": "battlecry; cheer; cry where one breathes in a large volume of air and then releases it suddenly in a loud cry\nrushing at the enemy" },
	{ "question": "呆気", "answers": [ "あっけ" ], "comment": "taken aback; dumbfounded" },
	{ "question": "呆然", "answers": [ "ぼうぜん" ], "comment": "dumbfounded; overcome with surprise; in blank amazement; in a daze" },
	{ "question": "呑む", "answers": [ "のむ" ], "comment": "to drink; to gulp; to swallow; to take (medicine)\nto smoke (tobacco)\nto engulf; to overwhelm\nto keep down; to suppress\nto accept (e.g. demand, condition)\nto make light of; to conceal" },
	{ "question": "呑気", "answers": [ "のんき" ], "comment": "carefree; optimistic; careless; reckless; heedless; happy-go-lucky; easygoing; thoughtless" },
	{ "question": "呟く", "answers": [ "つぶやく" ], "comment": "to mutter; to murmur; to grumble\nto tweet (Twitter)" },
	{ "question": "味噌", "answers": [ "みそ" ], "comment": "miso; fermented condiment usu. made from soybeans\ninnards (from crabs, shrimps, etc.) resembling miso\nkey (main) point; good part (of something)\nweakling; weak person" },
	{ "question": "味蕾", "answers": [ "みらい" ], "comment": "taste bud" },
	{ "question": "呵責", "answers": [ "かしゃく" ], "comment": "blame; accusation; torture; maltreatment; pangs (of conscience)" },
	{ "question": "呷る", "answers": [ "あおる" ], "comment": "to gulp down (a drink); to slurp" },
	{ "question": "呻く", "answers": [ "うめく" ], "comment": "to moan; to groan" },
	{ "question": "咀嚼", "answers": [ "そしゃく" ], "comment": "chewing; mastication\ndigestion (e.g. of words); assimilation; comprehension; appreciation" },
	{ "question": "咄嗟", "answers": [ "とっさ" ], "comment": "moment; instant" },
	{ "question": "咄嗟に", "answers": [ "とっさに" ], "comment": "at once; right away; promptly; on the spur of the moment" },
	{ "question": "咎める", "answers": [ "とがめる" ], "comment": "to blame; to reproach; to censure; to rebuke; to reprove; to find fault; to take to task; to criticize; to criticise\nto question (a suspect); to challenge\nto aggravate (an injury); to be aggravated; to get inflamed\nto prick (one's conscience)" },
	{ "question": "咥える", "answers": [ "くわえる" ], "comment": "to hold in one's mouth" },
	{ "question": "咳", "answers": [ "せき", "しわぶき" ], "comment": "cough; coughing; tussis" },
	{ "question": "咳く", "answers": [ "せく" ], "comment": "to cough" },
	{ "question": "唖然", "answers": [ "あぜん" ], "comment": "dumbfounded; in mute amazement" },
	{ "question": "唸る", "answers": [ "うなる" ], "comment": "to groan; to moan\nto roar; to howl; to growl\nto hum (e.g. engine, wires in wind); to buzz; to sough; low, dull sound\nto ooh and aah (in admiration)\nto sing in a strong, low voice (esp. traditional chant or recitation)" },
	{ "question": "啄む", "answers": [ "ついばむ" ], "comment": "to pick at; to peck at" },
	{ "question": "商人", "answers": [ "あきんど", "しょうにん" ], "comment": "trader; shopkeeper; merchant" },
	{ "question": "啓蒙", "answers": [ "けいもう" ], "comment": "enlightenment; instruction" },
	{ "question": "啖呵", "answers": [ "たんか" ], "comment": "caustic words" },
	{ "question": "啜る", "answers": [ "すする" ], "comment": "to sip; to slurp" },
	{ "question": "喇叭飲み", "answers": [ "らっぱのみ" ], "comment": "drinking straight from a bottle" },
	{ "question": "喉飴", "answers": [ "のどあめ" ], "comment": "throat lozenge; cough drop" },
	{ "question": "喋々する", "answers": [ "ちょうちょうする" ], "comment": "talk glibly;  talk volubly; chatter; jabber; babble; prate\nbe long-winded\nspeak at great length; dwell [enlarge] upon" },
	{ "question": "喋る", "answers": [ "しゃべる" ], "comment": "to talk; to chat; to chatter" },
	{ "question": "喘ぐ", "answers": [ "あえぐ" ], "comment": "to gasp; breathe hard\nto suffer; to struggle" },
	{ "question": "喘息", "answers": [ "ぜんそく" ], "comment": "asthma; phthisis" },
	{ "question": "喚く", "answers": [ "わめく", "おめく" ], "comment": "to shout; to cry; to scream; to clamour" },
	{ "question": "喧嘩", "answers": [ "けんか" ], "comment": "quarrel; brawl; fight; squabble; scuffle; argument" },
	{ "question": "喧噪", "answers": [ "けんそう" ], "comment": "tumult; great noise; clatter; hustle and bustle" },
	{ "question": "喰らう", "answers": [ "くらう" ], "comment": "to eat; to drink\nto receive (e.g. a blow)" },
	{ "question": "嗄れる", "answers": [ "しゃがれる", "かれる", "しわがれる" ], "comment": "to become hoarse\nto grow hoarse; to become husky" },
	{ "question": "嗚咽", "answers": [ "おえつ" ], "comment": "sobbing; weeping; groaning; fit of crying" },
	{ "question": "嗜む", "answers": [ "たしなむ" ], "comment": "to have a taste for; to be fond of; to have an interest in (e.g. a hobby)\nto be modest; to be prudent" },
	{ "question": "嗜好", "answers": [ "しこう" ], "comment": "taste; liking; preference" },
	{ "question": "嗜虐", "answers": [ "しぎゃく" ], "comment": "sadism" },
	{ "question": "嘘", "answers": [ "うそ" ], "comment": "lie; fib; falsehood; untruth\nmistake; error\nunwise move; bad decision\nNo way!; Unbelievable!; Really?!" },
	{ "question": "嘯く", "answers": [ "うそぶく" ], "comment": "to boast; to brag\nto recite (a song or poem to oneself)\nto bark; to roar; to howl" },
	{ "question": "嘱目", "answers": [ "しょくもく" ], "comment": "paying attention to; catching one's eye" },
	{ "question": "嘲る", "answers": [ "あざける" ], "comment": "to scoff; to laugh at; to make fun of; to ridicule; to jeer at" },
	{ "question": "嘴", "answers": [ "くちばし" ], "comment": "beak; bill" },
	{ "question": "嘶く", "answers": [ "いななく" ], "comment": "to neigh" },
	{ "question": "嘸や", "answers": [ "さぞや" ], "comment": "surely; certainly" },
	{ "question": "噂", "answers": [ "うわさ" ], "comment": "rumour; rumor; report; hearsay; gossip; common talk" },
	{ "question": "噛む", "answers": [ "かむ" ], "comment": "to bite; to chew; to gnaw\nto crash against (e.g. of waves); to break onto (shore)\nto engage (of cogs, zippers, etc.); to mesh; to fit together\nto be involved in\nto fumble one's words (during a play, broadcast, etc.); to falter with one's words\nto strongly confute; to argue down; to rebuke; to scold harshly\nto chew (strongly)" },
	{ "question": "噤む", "answers": [ "つぐむ" ], "comment": "to shut one's mouth; to hold one's tongue; to keep silent" },
	{ "question": "嚥下", "answers": [ "えんげ", "えんか" ], "comment": "(act of) swallowing; deglutition" },
	{ "question": "囀る", "answers": [ "さえずる" ], "comment": "to sing; to chirp; to twitter" },
	{ "question": "囁く", "answers": [ "ささやく" ], "comment": "to whisper; to murmur\nto rumor; to rumour" },
	{ "question": "囃す", "answers": [ "はやす" ], "comment": "to play accompaniment; to keep time\nto cheer; to applaud\nto jeer; to mock; to banter" },
	{ "question": "囓る", "answers": [ "かじる" ], "comment": "to gnaw; to nibble; to bite; to munch; to crunch\nto dabble in; to have a smattering of" },
	{ "question": "因む", "answers": [ "ちなむ" ], "comment": "to be associated (with); to be connected (with)" },
	{ "question": "団扇", "answers": [ "うちわ" ], "comment": "uchiwa; type of traditional Japanese handheld fan" },
	{ "question": "囮", "answers": [ "おとり" ], "comment": "decoy (for hunting); stool\nlure; decoy; stool pigeon; trap" },
	{ "question": "土竜", "answers": [ "もぐら" ], "comment": "mole (Talpidae spp., esp. the small Japanese mole, Mogera imaizumii)" },
	{ "question": "均す", "answers": [ "ならす" ], "comment": "to make even; to make smooth; to make level\nto average" },
	{ "question": "坐す", "answers": [ "まします", "ます", "います", "（ざす）" ], "comment": "to be implicated\nto be\nto be\nto go; to come\n(to sit; to squat)" },
	{ "question": "坩堝", "answers": [ "るつぼ" ], "comment": "crucible; (melting) pot" },
	{ "question": "垢", "answers": [ "あか" ], "comment": "dirt; filth; grime\naccount (e.g. online service)\nklesha (polluting thoughts such as greed, hatred and delusion, which result in suffering)" },
	{ "question": "埃", "answers": [ "ほこり" ], "comment": "dust\none ten-billionth" },
	{ "question": "埠頭", "answers": [ "ふとう" ], "comment": "pier; wharf; quay; dock" },
	{ "question": "塒", "answers": [ "ねぐら", "とや" ], "comment": "coil\nroost; nesting place" },
	{ "question": "塗す", "answers": [ "まぶす" ], "comment": "to cover (smear, sprinkle) (with)" },
	{ "question": "塩梅", "answers": [ "あんばい" ], "comment": "seasoning; flavour; flavor\nserving one's lord well (of a retainer)\nseasoning; flavour; flavor\ncondition; state; situation\narrangement; assignment; adjustment" },
	{ "question": "塵", "answers": [ "ちり", "ごみ" ], "comment": "rubbish; trash; garbage; refuse\ndust; dirt\ndefilement; impurity; affliction\nobject (perceived with the mind or the senses)\none billionth" },
	{ "question": "壺", "answers": [ "つぼ" ], "comment": "jar; pot; vase\ndice cup\ndepression (i.e. the basin of a waterfall)\ntarget (when aiming an arrow)\n(figurative) bull's-eye\nkey point (of a conversation, etc.)\nacupuncture point; moxibustion point\nnodes on a fingerboard (of a shamisen, etc.)\nhu (ancient Chinese vessel shaped like a vase, usually used to store alcohol)" },
	{ "question": "夕餉", "answers": [ "ゆうげ" ], "comment": "evening meal; supper; dinner" },
	{ "question": "外套", "answers": [ "がいとう" ], "comment": "overcoat; greatcoat; cloak; wrap; mantle" },
	{ "question": "夜伽", "answers": [ "よとぎ" ], "comment": "attending someone through the night (guard, nurse)\nact of a woman sleeping with a man (at his bidding)\nkeeping overnight vigil over body before burial" },
	{ "question": "夢現", "answers": [ "ゆめうつつ" ], "comment": "half asleep and half awake; trance\ndream and reality" },
	{ "question": "夥しい", "answers": [ "おびただしい" ], "comment": "large number; innumerable; great many; immense; vast; abundant" },
	{ "question": "大和撫子", "answers": [ "やまとなでしこ" ], "comment": "large pink (Dianthus superbus var. longicalycinus)\nwoman who displays the feminine virtues of old Japan" },
	{ "question": "大海原", "answers": [ "おおうなばら" ], "comment": "the ocean; the great deep" },
	{ "question": "大袈裟", "answers": [ "おおげさ" ], "comment": "grandiose; exaggerated" },
	{ "question": "天下る", "answers": [ "あまくだる" ], "comment": "to descend from heaven" },
	{ "question": "天秤", "answers": [ "てんびん" ], "comment": "(balance) scales\nshoulder carrying pole\nsteelyard" },
	{ "question": "太刀打ち", "answers": [ "たちうち" ], "comment": "crossing swords\ncompeting against; contending with; fighting against" },
	{ "question": "夭折", "answers": [ "ようせつ" ], "comment": "premature death" },
	{ "question": "奇天烈", "answers": [ "きてれつ" ], "comment": "very strange; odd; queer" },
	{ "question": "奢る", "answers": [ "おごる" ], "comment": "to give (someone) a treat\nto be extravagant; to live luxuriously\nto be proud; to be haughty" },
	{ "question": "奸計", "answers": [ "かんけい" ], "comment": "trick; evil design; sharp practice" },
	{ "question": "好事家", "answers": [ "こうずか" ], "comment": "dilettante; person of fantastic taste" },
	{ "question": "好敵手", "answers": [ "こうてきしゅ" ], "comment": "worthy rival or opponent" },
	{ "question": "如何せん", "answers": [ "いかんせん" ], "comment": "to one's regret; regrettably; unfortunately\nit cannot be helped" },
	{ "question": "如何わしい", "answers": [ "いかがわしい" ], "comment": "suspicious; dubious; unreliable\nindecent; unseemly" },
	{ "question": "妄りに", "answers": [ "みだりに" ], "comment": "without authority\nwithout reason; unnecessarily\nrecklessly; indiscriminately; arbitrarily" },
	{ "question": "妬む", "answers": [ "ねたむ", "そねむ" ], "comment": "to be jealous of; to envy; to begrudge" },
	{ "question": "妾", "answers": [ "めかけ", "わらわ", "そばめ" ], "comment": "I; me\nmistress; kept woman; concubine" },
	{ "question": "姪", "answers": [ "めい" ], "comment": "niece" },
	{ "question": "婉曲", "answers": [ "えんきょく" ], "comment": "euphemistic; circumlocutory; roundabout; indirect" },
	{ "question": "媚びる", "answers": [ "こびる" ], "comment": "to flatter; to curry favor with; to curry favour with; to fawn on; to butter up to\nto flirt with (woman with a man); to make eyes at (a man)" },
	{ "question": "媚薬", "answers": [ "びやく" ], "comment": "aphrodisiac\nlove potion; philter" },
	{ "question": "嫉む", "answers": [ "そねむ", "ねたむ" ], "comment": "to be jealous of; to envy; to begrudge" },
	{ "question": "嫉妬", "answers": [ "しっと" ], "comment": "jealousy; envy" },
	{ "question": "嬉々として", "answers": [ "ききとして" ] },　"comment": "happily; joyfully" },
	{ "question": "嬉しい", "answers": [ "うれしい" ], "comment": "happy; glad; pleasant" },
	{ "question": "嬲る", "answers": [ "なぶる" ], "comment": "to tease; to make fun of; to make sport of\nto torment; to blame; to persecute\nto tamper" },
	{ "question": "子守", "answers": [ "こもり" ], "comment": "nursemaid; nanny; babysitter\nchild-minding; babysitting" },
	{ "question": "孔雀", "answers": [ "くじゃく" ], "comment": "peafowl (incl. the male peacock, female peahen, and young peachick)" },
	{ "question": "孵る", "answers": [ "かえる" ], "comment": "to hatch out" },
	{ "question": "孵化", "answers": [ "ふか" ], "comment": "incubation; hatching" },
	{ "question": "安堵", "answers": [ "あんど" ], "comment": "relief; reassurance\nrecognition of right to land ownership (by the shogunate, a feudal lord, etc.)\nliving safely surrounded by walls" },
	{ "question": "宥める", "answers": [ "なだめる" ], "comment": "to soothe; to calm; to pacify" },
	{ "question": "容れ物", "answers": [ "いれもの" ], "comment": "container; case; receptacle\n(euph. for) coffin; casket" },
	{ "question": "容貌", "answers": [ "ようぼう" ], "comment": "looks; personal appearance; features" },
	{ "question": "密か", "answers": [ "ひそか", "みそか" ], "comment": "secret; private; surreptitious" },
	{ "question": "寛ぐ", "answers": [ "くつろぐ" ], "comment": "to relax; to feel at home" },
	{ "question": "寝癖", "answers": [ "ねぐせ" ], "comment": "bed hair; hair disarranged during sleep\nhabit of moving around in one's sleep; sleeping habit" },
	{ "question": "寝穢い", "answers": [ "いぎたない" ], "comment": "sound asleep; fast asleep\nuntidy; slovenly" },
	{ "question": "寧ろ", "answers": [ "むしろ" ], "comment": "rather; better; instead" },
	{ "question": "寵愛", "answers": [ "ちょうあい" ], "comment": "favor; favour; affection" },
	{ "question": "尖る", "answers": [ "とがる", "とんがる" ], "comment": "to taper to a point; to become sharp\nto look displeased; to look sour; to be on edge; to be touchy" },
	{ "question": "尖塔", "answers": [ "せんとう" ], "comment": "spire; steeple; pinnacle; minaret" },
	{ "question": "尤も", "answers": [ "もっとも" ], "comment": "but then; although; though\nreasonable; natural; just" },
	{ "question": "屁", "answers": [ "へ" ], "comment": "wind; gas; fart\nsomething worthless; something not worth considering" },
	{ "question": "居心地", "answers": [ "いごこち" ], "comment": "comfort" },
	{ "question": "屎尿", "answers": [ "しにょう" ], "comment": "excreta; raw sewage; human waste; night soil" },
	{ "question": "屏息", "answers": [ "へいそく" ], "comment": "bated breath; being cowed into silence" },
	{ "question": "屠る", "answers": [ "ほふる" ], "comment": "to slaughter; to massacre; to defeat; to butcher" },
	{ "question": "屠殺", "answers": [ "とさつ" ], "comment": "slaughter (of animals for meat)" },
	{ "question": "屯する", "answers": [ "たむろする" ], "comment": "to gather in large numbers (of people); to hang out (as a large group)\nto assemble (as a military unit or posse); to be quartered (in a particular location)" },
	{ "question": "峻厳", "answers": [ "しゅんげん" ], "comment": "strict; stern; rigorous; severe" },
	{ "question": "峻嶺", "answers": [ "しゅんれい" ], "comment": "steep peak; steep ridge; high rugged mountain" },
	{ "question": "崇める", "answers": [ "あがめる" ], "comment": "to revere; to respect; to worship" },
	{ "question": "嵩む", "answers": [ "かさむ" ], "comment": "to mount up; to pile up; to accumulate; to increase" },
	{ "question": "嵩張る", "answers": [ "かさばる" ], "comment": "to be bulky; to be unwieldy; to grow voluminous" },
	{ "question": "工夫する", "answers": [ "くふうする" ], "comment": "figure out / contrive / devise a good way (to handle a situation)" },
	{ "question": "差し支えない", "answers": [ "さしつかえない" ], "comment": "(having) no objection; allowable" },
	{ "question": "帰趨", "answers": [ "きすう", "きしゅ" ], "comment": "outcome (of a course of events); consequence\ntendency; trend; drift" },
	{ "question": "帰途", "answers": [ "きと" ], "comment": "on the way back; returning" },
	{ "question": "幇助", "answers": [ "ほうじょ" ], "comment": "assistance; backing\naiding and abetting (a crime); abetment" },
	{ "question": "平社員", "answers": [ "ひらしゃいん" ], "comment": "rank and file member of staff; ordinary employee; low-grade employee" },
	{ "question": "幸先", "answers": [ "さいさき" ], "comment": "omen; sign (usually good)" },
	{ "question": "庇う", "answers": [ "かばう" ], "comment": "to protect someone; to take under one's wing; to plead for; to stick up for; to cover up for someone" },
	{ "question": "庇護", "answers": [ "ひご" ], "comment": "patronage; protection" },
	{ "question": "店子", "answers": [ "たなこ" ], "comment": "tenant (esp. in contrast to a landlord); renter" },
	{ "question": "建立", "answers": [ "こんりゅう" ], "comment": "(act of) building (temple, monument, etc.); erection" },
	{ "question": "弁える", "answers": [ "わきまえる" ], "comment": "to know (right from wrong); to discern; to discriminate; to understand; to bear in mind" },
	{ "question": "弄る", "answers": [ "まさぐる", "いじる", "あなどる", "いじくる" ], "comment": "to touch; to tamper with\nto grope about; to feel for something\nto finger; to tamper (with)" },
	{ "question": "引っ掻く", "answers": [ "ひっかく" ], "comment": "to scratch; to claw" },
	{ "question": "弛む", "answers": [ "たるむ", "たゆむ", "ゆるむ" ], "comment": "to become loose; to slacken (e.g. rope)\nto become less tense; to relax; to let one's guard down\nto slacken (e.g. coldness, supervision); to become lax\nto become softer (e.g. ground, facial expression); (of ice) to partially melt\nto decrease (e.g. speed)\n(of a market price) to go down slightly\nto slacken; to loosen; to relax; to droop (e.g. loose or flabby skin); to sag (ceiling)\nto slack off (e.g. one's work, attention); to not put one's heart in" },
	{ "question": "弛緩", "answers": [ "しかん" ], "comment": "relaxation (e.g. of muscles); becoming flaccid" },
	{ "question": "強か", "answers": [ "したたか" ], "comment": "tough; stubborn; determined; hard\nseverely; heavily; hard; a great deal; much" },
	{ "question": "強ち", "answers": [ "あながち" ], "comment": "not necessarily; not uncommon" },
	{ "question": "強面", "answers": [ "こわもて" ], "comment": "hard-faced; aggressive; fierce look; frightening look" },
	{ "question": "強靭", "answers": [ "きょうじん" ], "comment": "tough; strong; stiff; tenacious" },
	{ "question": "彗星", "answers": [ "すいせい" ], "comment": "comet" },
	{ "question": "彷彿", "answers": [ "ほうふつ" ], "comment": "close resemblance; vivid reminder (e.g. of the past)" },
	{ "question": "徐ろに", "answers": [ "おもむろに" ], "comment": "suddenly; abruptly\ndeliberately; slowly; gently" },
	{ "question": "徒に", "answers": [ "いたずらに" ] }, "comment": "in vain; vainly; uselessly" },
	{ "question": "徒然", "answers": [ "つれづれ", "とぜん" ], "comment": "tedium" },
	{ "question": "御馳走", "answers": [ "ごちそう" ], "comment": "feast; treating (someone)\nto treat (someone, e.g. to a meal)" },
	{ "question": "復讐", "answers": [ "ふくしゅう" ], "comment": "revenge" },
	{ "question": "心底", "answers": [ "しんそこ" ], "comment": "bottom of one's heart; depths of one's mind; innermost thoughts\ncompletely (from the bottom of one's heart); truly" },
	{ "question": "忌憚", "answers": [ "きたん" ], "comment": "reserve; modesty" },
	{ "question": "忖度", "answers": [ "そんたく" ], "comment": "surmise (about somebody's feelings); guess; conjecture" },
	{ "question": "忙しない", "answers": [ "せわしない" ], "comment": "restless; fidgety; in a hurry" },
	{ "question": "忸怩", "answers": [ "じくじ" ], "comment": "bashful; shameful; ashamed" },
	{ "question": "忽然", "answers": [ "こつぜん" ], "comment": "sudden; unexpected" },
	{ "question": "怒濤", "answers": [ "どとう" ], "comment": "surging waves; raging billows\nleaps and bounds" },
	{ "question": "急く", "answers": [ "せく" ], "comment": "to hurry; to rush" },
	{ "question": "怨嗟", "answers": [ "えんさ" ], "comment": "(deeply held) resentment" },
	{ "question": "怪訝", "answers": [ "けげん" ], "comment": "dubious; puzzled; suspicious" },
	{ "question": "怯える", "answers": [ "おびえる" ], "comment": "to become frightened; to be frightened (of); to be scared (of)" },
	{ "question": "怯む", "answers": [ "ひるむ" ], "comment": "to falter; to flinch (from); to recoil (from); to quail (at)" },
	{ "question": "恍惚", "answers": [ "こうこつ" ], "comment": "ecstasy; trance" },
	{ "question": "恙無く", "answers": [ "つつがなく" ] }, "comment": "safely; in safety; safe and sound" },
	{ "question": "悄然", "answers": [ "しょうぜん" ], "comment": "dejected; dispirited; crestfallen; discouraged" },
	{ "question": "悍ましい", "answers": [ "おぞましい" ], "comment": "disgusting; repulsive" },
	{ "question": "悖る", "answers": [ "もとる" ], "comment": "to go against; to act contrary to; to deviate from; to oppose" },
	{ "question": "悴む", "answers": [ "かじかむ" ], "comment": "to grow numb with cold" },
	{ "question": "悶える", "answers": [ "もだえる" ], "comment": "to be in agony; to worry" },
	{ "question": "悶絶", "answers": [ "もんぜつ" ], "comment": "fainting in agony" },
	{ "question": "惚ける", "answers": [ "とぼける", "ぼける", "ほうける" ], "comment": "to grow senile; to be childish with age\nto be mentally slow; to be befuddled\nto play stupid; to say something stupid (oft. on purpose; esp. as part of a comedic routine)\nto become engrossed (in something)\nto play dumb; to feign ignorance; to play innocent; to have a blank facial expression\nto play the fool\nto be in one's dotage" },
	{ "question": "惚れる", "answers": [ "ほれる" ], "comment": "to fall in love; to be in love; to be charmed with; to lose one's heart to" },
	{ "question": "惚気", "answers": [ "のろけ" ], "comment": "speaking fondly of a loved one" },
	{ "question": "惹く", "answers": [ "ひく" ], "comment": "to attract; to captivate" },
	{ "question": "愛しい", "answers": [ "いとしい" ], "comment": "lovely; dear; beloved; darling" },
	{ "question": "愛でる", "answers": [ "めでる" ], "comment": "to love; to admire" },
	{ "question": "愛嬌", "answers": [ "あいきょう" ], "comment": "charm; attractiveness; amiability; winsomeness\ncourtesy; ingratiating behaviour\nentertainment; amusement; fun" },
	{ "question": "愛撫", "answers": [ "あいぶ" ], "comment": "caressing; loving dearly" },
	{ "question": "慇懃", "answers": [ "いんぎん" ], "comment": "courtesy; intimacy; friendship" },
	{ "question": "慟哭", "answers": [ "どうこく" ], "comment": "wailing; lamentation" },
	{ "question": "慧眼", "answers": [ "けいがん" ], "comment": "discerning (quick) eye; keen insight\nthe wisdom eye" },
	{ "question": "憎悪", "answers": [ "ぞうお" ], "comment": "hatred" },
	{ "question": "憐れむ", "answers": [ "あわれむ" ], "comment": "to commiserate; to pity; to have mercy on; to sympathize with; to sympathise with" },
	{ "question": "憐憫", "answers": [ "れんびん" ], "comment": "pity; compassion; mercy" },
	{ "question": "憑依", "answers": [ "ひょうい" ], "comment": "dependence; depending on\npossession (by a spirit, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "憔悴", "answers": [ "しょうすい" ], "comment": "emaciation; haggardness; wasting away\nexhaustion; tiredness" },
	{ "question": "憚る", "answers": [ "はばかる" ], "comment": "to hesitate; to have scruples; to be afraid of what others may think\nto lord it over; to have great influence" },
	{ "question": "成就", "answers": [ "じょうじゅ" ], "comment": "fulfillment; fulfilment; realization; realisation; completion" },
	{ "question": "戦く", "answers": [ "おののく" ], "comment": "to shake (from fear, cold, excitement, etc.); to shudder; to tremble\nto tremble; to shiver; to shake" },
	{ "question": "戦慄く", "answers": [ "わななく" ], "comment": "to tremble; to shiver; to shake" },
	{ "question": "戦禍を被る", "answers": [ "せんかをこうむる" ], "comment": "to be devastated/ravaged by war" },
	{ "question": "戯れ付く", "answers": [ "じゃれつく" ], "comment": "to be playful (of a child or animal); to play; to sport; to frolic" },
	{ "question": "所以", "answers": [ "ゆえん" ], "comment": "reason; way of doing; cause; grounds" },
	{ "question": "所謂", "answers": [ "いわゆる" ], "comment": "what is called; as it is called; the so-called; so to speak" },
	{ "question": "手強い", "answers": [ "てごわい" ], "comment": "difficult; tough; formidable; redoubtable; stubborn\nstrong; resolute; firm; strict" },
	{ "question": "手筈", "answers": [ "てはず" ], "comment": "arrangement; plan; programme; program" },
	{ "question": "扮する", "answers": [ "ふんする" ], "comment": "to dress up as; to disguise oneself as; to play the role of" },
	{ "question": "扼殺", "answers": [ "やくさつ" ], "comment": "strangulation" },
	{ "question": "承る", "answers": [ "うけたまわる" ], "comment": "to hear; to be told; to know\nto receive (order); to undertake; to comply; to take (a reservation, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "抉る", "answers": [ "えぐる" ], "comment": "to gouge; to hollow out; to bore; to excavate; to scoop out\nto greatly perturb; to cause emotional pain\nto get to the bottom of things; to relentlessly bring the truth to light\nto dig out; to gouge out; to hollow out\nto scoop; to ladle; to bail\nto jerk (one's chin)\nto pry; to prize; to prise\nto stick into and move around; to dig around in; to pick (i.e. one's teeth)" },
	{ "question": "抓る", "answers": [ "つねる", "つめる" ], "comment": "to pinch" },
	{ "question": "投じる", "answers": [ "とうじる" ], "comment": "to throw; to cast (e.g. vote, light, shadow)\nto devote oneself (e.g. to a cause)\nto invest; to put in\nto administer (medicine); to give\nto surrender\nto take advantage of; to make full use of\nto fit well with; to match with; to be in tune with\nto stay (at a lodging)" },
	{ "question": "投函", "answers": [ "とうかん" ], "comment": "mailing; posting" },
	{ "question": "投擲", "answers": [ "とうてき" ], "comment": "throwing; throwing event" },
	{ "question": "抜擢", "answers": [ "ばってき" ], "comment": "selection (esp. from many people for an important job position); exceptional promotion" },
	{ "question": "拉ぐ", "answers": [ "ひしぐ" ], "comment": "to crush" },
	{ "question": "拗ねる", "answers": [ "すねる" ], "comment": "to be peevish; to sulk; to pout" },
	{ "question": "招聘", "answers": [ "しょうへい" ], "comment": "(courteous) invitation; call\nto invite (with the utmost courtesy, e.g. an expert or professor to give a lecture)" },
	{ "question": "拷問", "answers": [ "ごうもん" ], "comment": "torture; the rack; third degree" },
	{ "question": "挽回", "answers": [ "ばんかい" ], "comment": "recovery; restoration" },
	{ "question": "捌ける", "answers": [ "さばける" ], "comment": "to sell well; to sell out\nto be in order\nto be sociable; to be worldly and understanding\nto flow smoothly\nto sell well; to sell out\nto exit the stage; to remove (a prop) from the stage" },
	{ "question": "捌け口", "answers": [ "はけぐち" ], "comment": "outlet (e.g. for water or gas)\nmarket (for something)\noutlet (e.g. for excess energy); vent (e.g. for emotions)" },
	{ "question": "捏ち上げる", "answers": [ "でっちあげる" ], "comment": "to fabricate; to invent; to make up (a story); to hoax; to pull a hoax\nto cobble up; to put together in a hurry" },
	{ "question": "捏ねる", "answers": [ "こねる" ], "comment": "to knead; to mix with fingers\nto quibble; to argue for argument's sake" },
	{ "question": "捏造", "answers": [ "ねつぞう" ], "comment": "fabrication; forgery; falsehood; hoax" },
	{ "question": "捗々しい", "answers": [ "はかばかしい" ], "comment": "quick; rapid; swift; satisfactory" },
	{ "question": "捗る", "answers": [ "はかどる" ], "comment": "to make progress; to move right ahead (with the work); to advance" },
	{ "question": "捧げる", "answers": [ "ささげる" ], "comment": "to lift up; to hold up; to hold above eye level\nto give; to offer; to consecrate\nto devote; to sacrifice; to dedicate" },
	{ "question": "捲る", "answers": [ "めくる", "まくる" ], "comment": "to turn up; to roll up (e.g. sleeves)\nto do relentlessly; to do with reckless abandon\nto stage a comeback (against) (in mahjong, horse racing, etc.); to come from behind\nto turn over; to turn pages of a book\nto tear off; to strip off; to tear up" },
	{ "question": "捻る", "answers": [ "ひねる", "ねじる" ], "comment": "to twist; to wrench; to turn (a switch on or off, etc.); to wring (a neck)\nto puzzle over\nto defeat easily\nto screw; to twist\nto distort; to parody; to make a pun\nto torture; to wrest" },
	{ "question": "捻出", "answers": [ "ねんしゅつ" ], "comment": "contriving (to raise funds, to find time, etc.)\nworking out (a solution)" },
	{ "question": "掌", "answers": [ "てのひら", "たなごころ" ], "comment": "palm (of one's hand)" },
	{ "question": "掣肘", "answers": [ "せいちゅう" ], "comment": "restraint; restriction; control" },
	{ "question": "推敲", "answers": [ "すいこう" ], "comment": "polishing (e.g. essay); revision; elaboration; refinement; improvement" },
	{ "question": "掬う", "answers": [ "すくう" ], "comment": "to scoop; to ladle out" },
	{ "question": "掴む", "answers": [ "つかむ" ], "comment": "to seize; to catch; to grasp; to grip; to grab; to clutch; to hold; to catch hold of; to lay one's hands on\nto obtain; to acquire; to get; to win; to capture\nto understand; to grasp; to comprehend" },
	{ "question": "掻い潜る", "answers": [ "かいくぐる" ], "comment": "to slip through" },
	{ "question": "掻く", "answers": [ "かく" ], "comment": "to scratch\nto perspire\nto shovel; to paddle" },
	{ "question": "掻っ込む", "answers": [ "かっこむ" ], "comment": "to bolt one's food; to gulp down" },
	{ "question": "揃う", "answers": [ "そろう" ], "comment": "to become complete; to be all present; to be a full set; to have everything at one's disposal\nto be equal; to be uniform\nto gather; to assemble" },
	{ "question": "揉む", "answers": [ "もむ" ], "comment": "to rub; to crumple\nto massage\nto argue; to have a heated discussion\nto train; to coach\nto jostle; to crowd; to shake; to rock\nto have various experiences (out in the world)" },
	{ "question": "揶揄", "answers": [ "やゆ" ], "comment": "banter; raillery; tease; ridicule; banter with" },
	{ "question": "摑む", "answers": [ "つかむ" ], "comment": "to seize; to catch; to grasp; to grip; to grab; to clutch; to hold; to catch hold of; to lay one's hands on\nto obtain; to acquire; to get; to win; to capture\nto understand; to grasp; to comprehend" },
	{ "question": "摩天楼", "answers": [ "まてんろう" ], "comment": "skyscraper" },
	{ "question": "撒く", "answers": [ "まく" ], "comment": "to scatter; to sprinkle; to strew\nto distribute (handbills, etc.); to spread (rumours, etc.)\nto give the slip; to throw off; to shake off; to lose" },
	{ "question": "撓む", "answers": [ "たわむ" ], "comment": "to bend; to warp\nto lose heart" },
	{ "question": "撥", "answers": [ "ばち" ], "comment": "plectrum; pick\ndrumstick for Japanese drums (e.g. taiko)" },
	{ "question": "撥ねる", "answers": [ "はねる" ], "comment": "to hit (e.g. to have a car hit someone); to run into\nto reject; to deny; to refuse\nto eliminate; to exclude; to leave out\nto flip; to splash; to splatter\nto decapitate; to behead\nto jump up\nto point or curl up (e.g. ends of hair)" },
	{ "question": "撫でる", "answers": [ "なでる" ], "comment": "to brush gently; to stroke; to caress" },
	{ "question": "擽ぐったい", "answers": [ "くすぐったい" ], "comment": "ticklish\nembarrassing" },
	{ "question": "支う", "answers": [ "かう" ], "comment": "to support; to prop up" },
	{ "question": "改竄", "answers": [ "かいざん" ], "comment": "alteration; falsification; faking" },
	{ "question": "敏捷", "answers": [ "びんしょう" ], "comment": "nimble; prompt; agile; quick; shrewd; smart" },
	{ "question": "救恤", "answers": [ "きゅうじゅつ" ], "comment": "relief; aid; assistance" },
	{ "question": "散蒔く", "answers": [ "ばらまく" ], "comment": "to scatter; to disseminate (e.g. a rumor); to spread (e.g. germs); to broadcast\nto distribute widely (e.g. leaflets); to hand out freely; to spend recklessly" },
	{ "question": "敬虔", "answers": [ "けいけん" ], "comment": "pious; devout; modest" },
	{ "question": "斃れる", "answers": [ "たおれる" ], "comment": "to be forced to bed (by illness, etc.)\nto die\nto go bankrupt; to be ruined; to have a bad debt\nto be defeated (in a game)\nto fall (of governments, dictators, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "文鎮", "answers": [ "ぶんちん" ], "comment": "paperweight" },
	{ "question": "斡旋", "answers": [ "あっせん" ], "comment": "kind offices; services; through the good offices of; influence\nintercession; mediation" },
	{ "question": "戦斧", "answers": [ "せんぷ", "いくさおの" ], "comment": "battleaxe" },
	{ "question": "斧", "answers": [ "おの" ], "comment": "axe; hatchet" },
	{ "question": "一斤", "answers": [ "いっきん" ], "comment": "1 kin (~0.6kg)\n1 loaf of bread" },
	{ "question": "新嘗祭", "answers": [ "にいなめさい" ], "comment": "ceremonial offering by the Emperor of newly-harvested rice to the deities" },
	{ "question": "旋毛", "answers": [ "つむじ" ], "comment": "whorl of hair on the (back of the) head" },
	{ "question": "旺盛", "answers": [ "おうせい" ], "comment": "full of vim and vigor" },
	{ "question": "昔日", "answers": [ "せきじつ" ], "comment": "old days" },
	{ "question": "昼飯", "answers": [ "ひるめし" ], "comment": "lunch; midday meal" },
	{ "question": "晒す", "answers": [ "さらす" ], "comment": "to expose (to the sun, public, danger, etc.)\nto bleach; to refine\nto rinse (vegetables); to soak\nto sentence someone to public humiliation" },
	{ "question": "晩餐", "answers": [ "ばんさん" ], "comment": "dinner" },
	{ "question": "普く", "answers": [ "あまねく" ], "comment": "widely; generally; universally; far and wide" },
	{ "question": "暗澹", "answers": [ "あんたん" ], "comment": "dark; gloomy; somber; depressing" },
	{ "question": "暴露", "answers": [ "ばくろ" ], "comment": "disclosure; exposure; revelation" },
	{ "question": "曖昧", "answers": [ "あいまい" ], "comment": "vague; ambiguous; unclear\nfuzzy" },
	{ "question": "曝け出す", "answers": [ "さらけだす" ], "comment": "to expose; to disclose; to lay bare; to confess" },
	{ "question": "曝す", "answers": [ "さらす" ], "comment": "to expose (to the sun, public, danger, etc.)\nto bleach; to refine\nto rinse (vegetables); to soak\nto sentence someone to public humiliation\nto expose to the wind; to dry (something) in the wind" },
	{ "question": "有り体", "answers": [ "ありてい" ], "comment": "the unvarnished truth" },
	{ "question": "朋輩", "answers": [ "ほうばい" ], "comment": "comrade; friend; associate; colleague; fellow student; fellow apprentice" },
	{ "question": "朦朧", "answers": [ "もうろう" ], "comment": "dim; hazy; vague; indistinct; ambiguous; faint; obscure" },
	{ "question": "朧", "answers": [ "おぼろ" ], "comment": "hazy; dim; faint\nminced meat; minced fish" },
	{ "question": "木漏れ日", "answers": [ "こもれび" ], "comment": "sunlight filtering through trees" },
	{ "question": "木綿", "answers": [ "もめん" ], "comment": "cotton (material)\nred silk-cotton tree (Bombax ceiba)\nstring made of cut steamed, soaked mulberry bark fibers" },
	{ "question": "未曾有", "answers": [ "みぞう" ], "comment": "unprecedented; unheard of" },
	{ "question": "杖", "answers": [ "つえ" ], "comment": "cane; walking stick; staff; wand\nsevere caning (60-100 times)" },
	{ "question": "杭", "answers": [ "くい", "くいぜ" ], "comment": "stake; post; pile; picket" },
	{ "question": "松葉杖", "answers": [ "まつばづえ" ], "comment": "crutch; crutches" },
	{ "question": "枢機卿", "answers": [ "すうききょう" ], "comment": "cardinal (Catholic church)" },
	{ "question": "某", "answers": [ "それがし", "くれ", "なにがし", "ぼう" ], "comment": "someone; unknown person\nI; personal pronoun (used by samurai)\ncertain; one\ncertain amount; some\ncertain person; Mr So-and-so; a certain ...\nI; me" },
	{ "question": "柑橘", "answers": [ "かんきつ" ], "comment": "citrus; citrus fruit" },
	{ "question": "柑橘類", "answers": [ "かんきつるい" ], "comment": "citrus fruits" },
	{ "question": "柔な", "answers": [ "やわな" ] }, "comment": "soft; frail; fragile; weak; easily breakable; rickety" },
	{ "question": "栗", "answers": [ "くり" ], "comment": "Japanese chestnut (Castanea crenata)" },
	{ "question": "栗鼠", "answers": [ "りす" ], "comment": "squirrel (excluding flying squirrels)\nJapanese squirrel (Sciurus lis)" },
	{ "question": "桐", "answers": [ "きり" ], "comment": "paulownia tree; Paulownia tomentosa" },
	{ "question": "桶", "answers": [ "おけ" ], "comment": "bucket" },
	{ "question": "梁", "answers": [ "はり", "うつばり" ], "comment": "beam; joist\nLiang Dynasty (of China)" },
	{ "question": "梟", "answers": [ "ふくろう" ], "comment": "owl (esp. the Ural owl, Strix uralensis)" },
	{ "question": "梯子", "answers": [ "はしご" ], "comment": "ladder\nstairs\ngoing to several places in succession (e.g. barhopping)" },
	{ "question": "棲む", "answers": [ "すむ" ], "comment": "to live (of animals); to inhabit; to nest" },
	{ "question": "棺", "answers": [ "ひつぎ" ], "comment": "coffin; casket" },
	{ "question": "棺桶", "answers": [ "かんおけ" ], "comment": "coffin; casket" },
	{ "question": "楔", "answers": [ "くさび" ], "comment": "wedge; chock; linchpin; lynchpin\ntie; bond" },
	{ "question": "楕円", "answers": [ "だえん" ], "comment": "ellipse" },
	{ "question": "標榜", "answers": [ "ひょうぼう" ], "comment": "standing for; advocating; championing; professing (to be)" },
	{ "question": "横溢", "answers": [ "おういつ" ], "comment": "overflowing; inundation" },
	{ "question": "横行", "answers": [ "おうこう" ], "comment": "walking sideways; staggering; striding\nbeing rampant; being widespread; being prevalent" },
	{ "question": "樫", "answers": [ "かし" ], "comment": "evergreen oak" },
	{ "question": "樽", "answers": [ "たる" ], "comment": "cask; barrel" },
	{ "question": "橇", "answers": [ "そり" ], "comment": "sleigh; sled; sledge\nsnow-shoes" },
	{ "question": "檻", "answers": [ "おり" ], "comment": "cage; pen; jail cell; gaol cell" },
	{ "question": "櫂", "answers": [ "かい" ], "comment": "paddle; oar; scull" },
	{ "question": "櫛", "answers": [ "くし" ], "comment": "comb" },
	{ "question": "欺瞞", "answers": [ "ぎまん" ], "comment": "deception; deceit" },
	{ "question": "歩哨", "answers": [ "ほしょう" ], "comment": "sentry" },
	{ "question": "歪", "answers": [ "いびつ" ], "comment": "distorted; crooked; irregular; warped\noval; elliptical shape\nround, wooden container for cooked rice\noval coin" },
	{ "question": "歪める", "answers": [ "ゆがめる" ], "comment": "to bend; to curve; to warp; to distort; to disfigure\nto bend (the truth); to falsify; to twist\nto corrupt; to sully" },
	{ "question": "歪曲", "answers": [ "わいきょく" ], "comment": "distortion; falsification; perversion" },
	{ "question": "殆ど", "answers": [ "ほとんど" ], "comment": "mostly; nearly; practically; well-nigh; almost invariably; all but; just about; almost" },
	{ "question": "殉教", "answers": [ "じゅんきょう" ], "comment": "martyrdom" },
	{ "question": "殺戮", "answers": [ "さつりく" ], "comment": "slaughter; massacre" },
	{ "question": "毅然", "answers": [ "きぜん" ], "comment": "fortitude; firmness; resolution" },
	{ "question": "比喩", "answers": [ "ひゆ" ], "comment": "simile; metaphor; allegory; parable" },
	{ "question": "毛糸", "answers": [ "けいと" ], "comment": "knitting wool; woollen yarn" },
	{ "question": "毟る", "answers": [ "むしる" ], "comment": "to pluck; to pick; to tear" },
	{ "question": "気色ばむ", "answers": [ "けしきばむ" ], "comment": "to grow angry; to display one's anger" },
	{ "question": "氷柱", "answers": [ "つらら", "ひょうちゅう" ], "comment": "icicle\nice pillar\nice" },
	{ "question": "汚穢", "answers": [ "おわい", "おあい", "おえ", "おかい" ], "comment": "night soil\nmuck; filth; dirt" },
	{ "question": "汲む", "answers": [ "くむ" ], "comment": "to draw (water); to fetch (water); to ladle; to dip; to scoop; to pump\nto have a drink together\nto consider; to sympathize with; to sympathise with" },
	{ "question": "油田", "answers": [ "ゆでん" ], "comment": "oil field" },
	{ "question": "況して", "answers": [ "まして" ], "comment": "still more; to say nothing of; not to mention\nstill less" },
	{ "question": "洒落", "answers": [ "しゃれ", "しゃらく" ], "comment": "frank; open-hearted\njoke; pun; witticism\nsmartly dressed; stylish; fashion-conscious; refined\nimpertinent\nfresh; fashionable\nprostitute" },
	{ "question": "洟", "answers": [ "はな" ], "comment": "snivel; nasal mucus; snot" },
	{ "question": "洩れる", "answers": [ "もれる" ], "comment": "to leak out; to escape; to come through; to shine through; to filter out\nto find expression; to give vent\nto leak out; to be divulged; to be disclosed\nto be omitted; to be left out; to be excluded; to be not included" },
	{ "question": "流布", "answers": [ "るふ" ], "comment": "circulation; dissemination" },
	{ "question": "流暢", "answers": [ "りゅうちょう" ], "comment": "fluent (language skill); flowing" },
	{ "question": "浮気", "answers": [ "うわき" ], "comment": "extramarital sex; affair; fooling around\ninfidelity; wantonness; unfaithfulness; inconstancy; fickleness; caprice" },
	{ "question": "涎", "answers": [ "よだれ", "よだり" ], "comment": "drool" },
	{ "question": "淀む", "answers": [ "よどむ" ], "comment": "to stagnate; to be stagnant; to settle; to deposit; to be sedimented; to be precipitated; to hesitate; to be sluggish; to stammer; to stumble; to falter" },
	{ "question": "淘汰", "answers": [ "とうた" ], "comment": "weeding out; elimination (e.g. of unneeded employees); culling; selection\nselection (e.g. natural selection)" },
	{ "question": "深淵", "answers": [ "しんえん" ], "comment": "abyss; ravine" },
	{ "question": "淵", "answers": [ "ふち" ], "comment": "deep pool; deep water; abyss\ndepths (e.g. of despair, etc.); grip (e.g. of death)" },
	{ "question": "淹れる", "answers": [ "いれる" ], "comment": "to make (tea, coffee, etc.); to brew a beverage (with hot water)" },
	{ "question": "清楚", "answers": [ "せいそ" ], "comment": "neat and clean; tidy; trim" },
	{ "question": "清澄", "answers": [ "せいちょう" ], "comment": "clear; serene" },
	{ "question": "湛える", "answers": [ "たたえる" ], "comment": "to fill (to the brim)\nto express (an emotion); to look (sad, glad); to wear (a smile)" },
	{ "question": "湯浴み", "answers": [ "ゆあみ" ], "comment": "(taking a) bath; hot spring cure" },
	{ "question": "満身創痍", "answers": [ "まんしんそうい" ], "comment": "having wounds all over one's body" },
	{ "question": "満遍なく", "answers": [ "まんべんなく" ], "comment": "equally; thoroughly; all over; uniformly; without exception; all around" },
	{ "question": "溜める", "answers": [ "ためる" ], "comment": "to amass; to accumulate; to store\nto leave unpaid" },
	{ "question": "溜息", "answers": [ "ためいき" ], "comment": "sigh" },
	{ "question": "溜飲", "answers": [ "りゅういん" ], "comment": "water brash; sour stomach" },
	{ "question": "溢れる", "answers": [ "あふれる", "こぼれる", "あぶれる" ], "comment": "to fail (in getting a job); to miss out (at fishing, hunting, etc.)\nto be left out; to be crowded out\nto overflow; to brim over; to flood\nto spill; to fall out of; to overflow\nto peek through; to become visible (although normally not)\nto escape (of a smile, tear, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "滂沱", "answers": [ "ぼうだ" ], "comment": "floods of tears, sweat, etc." },
	{ "question": "滔々", "answers": [ "とうとう" ], "comment": "torrentially; swiftly flowing (water, esp. river); voluminously flowing\n(speak) eloquently; fluently; spout forth (a torrent of speech)\nflood of the times (moving strongly in one direction); current of the times" },
	{ "question": "滲む", "answers": [ "にじむ" ], "comment": "to run (of liquid); to spread\nto blur; to blot; to be blurred\nto ooze; to well up (of tears, etc.)\nto show through (of feelings, emotions, etc.); to reveal itself" },
	{ "question": "滾る", "answers": [ "たぎる" ], "comment": "to boil; to seethe\nto roil (e.g. waterfall, torrent); to foam; to cascade down\nto well up (of emotions); to overflow (e.g. fighting spirit); to seethe (esp. blood)" },
	{ "question": "漁る", "answers": [ "あさる", "いさる", "すなどる" ], "comment": "to fish\nto look for; to search for; to hunt for; to scavenge; to scrounge; to look through; to rummage through\nto go on a spree (spending, reading, etc.); to binge" },
	{ "question": "漉す", "answers": [ "こす" ], "comment": "to filter; to strain" },
	{ "question": "漏洩", "answers": [ "ろうえい" ], "comment": "disclosure; leak (of information); divulging\nleakage (e.g. of gas or liquids); leak; escape (e.g. of gas); coming in (through) (e.g. of light)" },
	{ "question": "漕ぐ", "answers": [ "こぐ" ], "comment": "to row; to scull; to paddle\nto pedal (e.g. bicycle)\nto swing (on a swing)\nto operate a hand pump\nto push through (deep snow, the jungle, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "漲る", "answers": [ "みなぎる" ], "comment": "to be full to the brim; to overflow; to swell (e.g. river full of water)\nto be filled with (emotion, e.g. energy, passion, ardor); to be (brim) full of; to pervade (e.g. atmosphere with emotion)" },
	{ "question": "漸く", "answers": [ "ようやく" ], "comment": "finally; at last\nbarely; narrowly; hardly; only just\ngradually; little by little; by degrees" },
	{ "question": "潮騒", "answers": [ "しおさい", "しおざい" ], "comment": "sea roar" },
	{ "question": "澱粉", "answers": [ "でんぷん" ], "comment": "starch" },
	{ "question": "濡れる", "answers": [ "ぬれる" ], "comment": "to get wet" },
	{ "question": "濡れ衣", "answers": [ "ぬれぎぬ" ], "comment": "false accusations; unfounded suspicion; groundless charge\nwet clothes" },
	{ "question": "濯ぐ", "answers": [ "すすぐ", "ゆすぐ", "そそぐ" ], "comment": "to rinse; to wash out\nto have one's revenge; to wipe out a disgrace" },
	{ "question": "濾過", "answers": [ "ろか" ], "comment": "filtration; filtering; percolation" },
	{ "question": "瀕死", "answers": [ "ひんし" ], "comment": "dying; (on the) verge of death" },
	{ "question": "瀟洒", "answers": [ "しょうしゃ" ], "comment": "stylish; smart; elegant; chic; refined; trim; neat" },
	{ "question": "火傷", "answers": [ "やけど" ], "comment": "burn; scald" },
	{ "question": "灰燼", "answers": [ "かいじん" ], "comment": "ash; embers; complete destruction" },
	{ "question": "炒める", "answers": [ "いためる" ], "comment": "to fry; to saute; to stir-fry" },
	{ "question": "炒る", "answers": [ "いる" ], "comment": "to parch; to fry; to fire; to broil; to roast; to boil down (in oil)" },
	{ "question": "炙る", "answers": [ "あぶる" ], "comment": "to warm (e.g. one's hands over a fire); to dry\nto scorch; to broil; to toast; to grill" },
	{ "question": "炸裂", "answers": [ "さくれつ" ], "comment": "explosion; bursting" },
	{ "question": "点す", "answers": [ "ともす" ], "comment": "to light; to turn on\nto pour; to add (liquid); to serve (drinks)\nto put on (lipstick, etc.); to apply; to colour; to dye\nto light (a fire); to burn" },
	{ "question": "為替", "answers": [ "かわせ" ], "comment": "money order; draft\nexchange (e.g. foreign)" },
	{ "question": "烏合の衆", "answers": [ "うごうのしゅう" ], "comment": "disorderly crowd; mob" },
	{ "question": "烏滸がましい", "answers": [ "おこがましい" ], "comment": "presumptuous; impertinent; ridiculous; absurd" },
	{ "question": "烙印", "answers": [ "らくいん" ], "comment": "brand; mark" },
	{ "question": "焚き火", "answers": [ "たきび" ], "comment": "open-air fire (e.g. for garden refuse); bonfire\nopen fire (e.g. in a kitchen)" },
	{ "question": "無辜", "answers": [ "むこ" ], "comment": "innocent; blameless; guiltless" },
	{ "question": "然し", "answers": [ "しかし" ], "comment": "however; but" },
	{ "question": "焼べる", "answers": [ "くべる" ], "comment": "to throw on the fire; to burn" },
	{ "question": "煉瓦", "answers": [ "れんが" ], "comment": "brick" },
	{ "question": "煌びやか", "answers": [ "きらびやか" ], "comment": "gorgeous; gaudy; dazzling; gay; resplendent" },
	{ "question": "煌めく", "answers": [ "きらめく" ], "comment": "to glitter; to glisten; to sparkle; to twinkle; to glare; to gleam" },
	{ "question": "煎じる", "answers": [ "せんじる" ], "comment": "to boil; to decoct; to infuse" },
	{ "question": "煤", "answers": [ "すす" ], "comment": "soot" },
	{ "question": "煽てる", "answers": [ "おだてる" ], "comment": "to flatter; to soft-soap\nto instigate; to stir up" },
	{ "question": "煽る", "answers": [ "あおる" ], "comment": "to fan (oneself, flames, etc.)\nto flap; to be shaken (by wind)\nto instigate; to stir up; to agitate; to induce\nto buy a large amount in order to cause prices to rise\nto take a photo from a low angle\nto tailgate" },
	{ "question": "熾す", "answers": [ "おこす" ], "comment": "to build (a fire); to make; to start; to light" },
	{ "question": "燠", "answers": [ "おき" ], "comment": "embers; live charcoal" },
	{ "question": "燻す", "answers": [ "いぶす" ], "comment": "to smoke (something); to fumigate\nto oxidize; to oxidise" },
	{ "question": "燻る", "answers": [ "いぶる", "くすぶる" ], "comment": "to smoke; to smoulder; to smolder; to sputter\nto be sooty; to be smoke-stained\nto smoulder (e.g. a dispute); to smolder\nto seclude oneself\nto live in obscurity; to stay in the same level (of social position, circumstances, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "燻製", "answers": [ "くんせい" ], "comment": "smoked food; smoking (fish, meat, etc.)\nsmoked" },
	{ "question": "爛れる", "answers": [ "ただれる" ], "comment": "to be sore; to be inflamed; to be bleary; to fester\nto be dissipated; to be dissolute; to indulge in" },
	{ "question": "爪楊枝", "answers": [ "つまようじ" ], "comment": "toothpick" },
	{ "question": "爬虫類", "answers": [ "はちゅうるい" ], "comment": "reptiles" },
	{ "question": "牛痘", "answers": [ "ぎゅうとう" ], "comment": "cow pox; vaccinia" },
	{ "question": "物臭", "answers": [ "ものぐさ" ], "comment": "laziness; lazy person" },
	{ "question": "牽制", "answers": [ "けんせい" ], "comment": "check; restraint; constraint; diversion; feint; screen" },
	{ "question": "狡い", "answers": [ "ずるい", "こすい" ], "comment": "sly; cunning; dishonest; sneaky; crafty; unfair\nmiserly" },
	{ "question": "狡猾", "answers": [ "こうかつ" ], "comment": "sly; cunning; crafty" },
	{ "question": "狩人", "answers": [ "かりゅうど", "かりうど" ], "comment": "hunter" },
	{ "question": "狼", "answers": [ "おおかみ" ], "comment": "wolf (Canis lupus)\nwolf in sheep's clothing; womanizer" },
	{ "question": "狼煙", "answers": [ "のろし" ], "comment": "beacon; skyrocket; signal fire; smoke signals\nstarting shot; starting signal" },
	{ "question": "狼狽", "answers": [ "ろうばい" ], "comment": "confusion; dismay; consternation; panic" },
	{ "question": "狼狽える", "answers": [ "うろたえる" ], "comment": "to be flustered; to lose one's presence of mind" },
	{ "question": "狼藉", "answers": [ "ろうぜき", "ろうじゃく" ], "comment": "violence; outrage; riot; confusion; disorder" },
	{ "question": "猊下", "answers": [ "げいか" ], "comment": "your highness; your grace; your eminence" },
	{ "question": "猖獗", "answers": [ "しょうけつ" ], "comment": "spreading; infesting; running rampant" },
	{ "question": "猛禽", "answers": [ "もうきん" ], "comment": "bird of prey" },
	{ "question": "猥褻", "answers": [ "わいせつ" ], "comment": "obscenity" },
	{ "question": "獰猛", "answers": [ "どうもう" ], "comment": "ferocious; fierce; truculent; savage" },
	{ "question": "玄人", "answers": [ "くろうと" ], "comment": "expert; professional; master\nwoman in the nightlife business; demimondaine; geisha and prostitutes" },
	{ "question": "玉葱", "answers": [ "たまねぎ" ], "comment": "onion (Allium cepa)" },
	{ "question": "瑕疵", "answers": [ "かし" ], "comment": "flaw; defect; blemish" },
	{ "question": "瑣末", "answers": [ "さまつ" ], "comment": "trivial; trifling" },
	{ "question": "瓢箪", "answers": [ "ひょうたん" ], "comment": "gourd; calabash (Lagenaria siceraria var. gourda)" },
	{ "question": "甘党", "answers": [ "あまとう" ], "comment": "(someone with a) sweet tooth; person fond of sweets; person who doesn't like alcohol, preferring sweets" },
	{ "question": "生る", "answers": [ "なる" ], "comment": "to bear fruit" },
	{ "question": "生粋", "answers": [ "きっすい" ], "comment": "pure; genuine; trueborn; natural-born" },
	{ "question": "産毛", "answers": [ "うぶげ" ], "comment": "soft, downy hair (i.e. such as on one's cheek); peach fuzz; fluff; pappus\nlanugo\nlanuginous; pappose; pappous" },
	{ "question": "甥", "answers": [ "おい" ], "comment": "nephew" },
	{ "question": "甲冑", "answers": [ "かっちゅう" ], "comment": "armor and helmet (armour)" },
	{ "question": "甲斐性", "answers": [ "かいしょう" ], "comment": "resourcefulness; ability (esp. to earn a living); dependability; reliability" },
	{ "question": "画鋲", "answers": [ "がびょう" ], "comment": "drawing pin; thumb tack" },
	{ "question": "界隈", "answers": [ "かいわい" ], "comment": "neighborhood; neighbourhood; vicinity" },
	{ "question": "畏怖", "answers": [ "いふ" ], "comment": "awe; fear; fright" },
	{ "question": "番える", "answers": [ "つがえる" ], "comment": "to nock (an arrow); to fix an arrow to the string" },
	{ "question": "疎ら", "answers": [ "まばら" ], "comment": "sparse; thin; scattered; straggling; sporadic" },
	{ "question": "疼く", "answers": [ "うずく" ], "comment": "to throb; to ache" },
	{ "question": "疼痛", "answers": [ "とうつう" ], "comment": "pain" },
	{ "question": "痒い", "answers": [ "かゆい", "かいい" ], "comment": "itchy" },
	{ "question": "痘痕", "answers": [ "あばた", "いも", "とうこん" ], "comment": "pockmark\nsmallpox; variola\npockmark; pock" },
	{ "question": "痙攣", "answers": [ "けいれん" ], "comment": "convulsion; cramp; spasm; twitch; fit" },
	{ "question": "痛痒", "answers": [ "つうよう" ], "comment": "pain and itching\nmental anguish; unhealthy emotions" },
	{ "question": "痺れる", "answers": [ "しびれる" ], "comment": "to become numb; to go to sleep (e.g. a limb)\nto be excited; to be titillated; to be mesmerized" },
	{ "question": "癇癪", "answers": [ "かんしゃく" ], "comment": "passion; temper; irritability" },
	{ "question": "癌", "answers": [ "がん" ], "comment": "cancer" },
	{ "question": "百姓", "answers": [ "ひゃくしょう" ], "comment": "farmer; peasant; country bumpkin\nfarming\nthe common people\nthe common people\nimperial subjects; the people" },
	{ "question": "皹", "answers": [ "あかがり", "あかぎれ", "ひび", "ひびり", "ひみ" ], "comment": "crack; fissure\nrift; split\nchaps; skin fissure" },
	{ "question": "皺", "answers": [ "しわ", "しぼ" ], "comment": "wrinkle; crease\nripple\nbumpy texture of a material (esp. woven fabric)\ncreases in an eboshi hat" },
	{ "question": "益々", "answers": [ "ますます" ], "comment": "increasingly; more and more; decreasingly (when declining); less and less" },
	{ "question": "益体もない", "answers": [ "やくたいもない" ], "comment": "useless; worthless; absurd; baloney" },
	{ "question": "目眩", "answers": [ "めまい" ], "comment": "dizziness; giddiness; vertigo" },
	{ "question": "目蓋", "answers": [ "まぶた" ], "comment": "eyelid; eyelids" },
	{ "question": "目論見", "answers": [ "もくろみ" ], "comment": "plan; scheme; project; program; programme; intention; goal" },
	{ "question": "直截", "answers": [ "ちょくせつ" ], "comment": "direct; frank; straightforward; plain\ndecisive; prompt" },
	{ "question": "直談判", "answers": [ "じかだんぱん" ], "comment": "direct talks" },
	{ "question": "相槌", "answers": [ "あいづち" ], "comment": "aizuchi; back-channeling; interjections indicating that one is paying attention\ntwo smiths hammering at an object in turn" },
	{ "question": "眩しい", "answers": [ "まぶしい" ], "comment": "dazzling; radiant" },
	{ "question": "眼窩", "answers": [ "がんか" ], "comment": "eye socket; orbit" },
	{ "question": "睥睨", "answers": [ "へいげい" ], "comment": "glaring at; lording over" },
	{ "question": "睦まじい", "answers": [ "むつまじい" ], "comment": "harmonious; happy; affectionate" },
	{ "question": "睨む", "answers": [ "にらむ" ], "comment": "to glare at; to scowl at; to glower at\nto stare intensely at; to examine carefully\nto estimate; to guess; to suspect; to judge\nto keep an eye on someone (e.g. a suspicious or untrustworthy person); to watch\nto take account of; to take into consideration" },
	{ "question": "睫毛", "answers": [ "まつげ" ], "comment": "eyelashes" },
	{ "question": "瞑る", "answers": [ "つぶる", "つむる" ], "comment": "to close (eyes); to shut" },
	{ "question": "瞠る", "answers": [ "みはる" ], "comment": "to open one's eyes wide" },
	{ "question": "瞼", "answers": [ "まぶた" ], "comment": "eyelid; eyelids" },
	{ "question": "矮小", "answers": [ "わいしょう" ], "comment": "diminutive; pygmy; pigmy; stunted" },
	{ "question": "矮性", "answers": [ "わいせい" ], "comment": "dwarfism\ndwarf; stunted; diminutive" },
	{ "question": "石鹸", "answers": [ "せっけん" ], "comment": "soap" },
	{ "question": "研鑽", "answers": [ "けんさん" ], "comment": "diligent study; devoting oneself to one's studies" },
	{ "question": "硝子", "answers": [ "がらす" ], "comment": "glass; pane\nvitreous" },
	{ "question": "硫黄", "answers": [ "いおう" ], "comment": "sulfur (S); sulphur" },
	{ "question": "碌に", "answers": [ "ろくに" ], "comment": "well; enough; sufficiently" },
	{ "question": "碗", "answers": [ "わん" ], "comment": "bowl (ceramic, porcelain)" },
	{ "question": "碧眼", "answers": [ "へきがん" ], "comment": "blue eyes" },
	{ "question": "磔", "answers": [ "はりつけ" ], "comment": "crucifixion" },
	{ "question": "磯", "answers": [ "いそ" ], "comment": "(rocky) beach; seashore" },
	{ "question": "磯巾着", "answers": [ "いそぎんちゃく" ], "comment": "sea anemone" },
	{ "question": "礫", "answers": [ "つぶて" ], "comment": "pebble\nstone (used for throwing)" },
	{ "question": "祀る", "answers": [ "まつる" ], "comment": "to deify; to enshrine\nto pray; to worship" },
	{ "question": "祈祷", "answers": [ "きとう" ], "comment": "prayer; grace (at meals)\nexorcism" },
	{ "question": "祓う", "answers": [ "はらう" ], "comment": "to exorcise; to cleanse; to purify" },
	{ "question": "祟る", "answers": [ "たたる" ], "comment": "to curse; to cast a spell; to haunt; to torment\nto cause a bad result; to bring about a negative outcome" },
	{ "question": "祭祀", "answers": [ "さいし" ], "comment": "ritual; religious service; festival" },
	{ "question": "禄", "answers": [ "ろく" ], "comment": "stipend; reward" },
	{ "question": "禿げる", "answers": [ "はげる" ], "comment": "to lose hair; to become bald\nto become bare (e.g. a mountain becomes bare of trees)" },
	{ "question": "禿髪", "answers": [ "とくはつ" ], "comment": "baldness; balding; bald head" },
	{ "question": "秤", "answers": [ "はかり" ], "comment": "scales; weighing machine" },
	{ "question": "称える", "answers": [ "たたえる", "となえる" ], "comment": "to extol; to give praise\nto assume the name of" },
	{ "question": "稀に", "answers": [ "まれに" ] }, "comment": "rarely; seldom; uncommonly; on rare occasions; at rare intervals" },
	{ "question": "稲妻", "answers": [ "いなずま", "いなづま" ], "comment": "lightning; flash of lightning; lightning bolt" },
	{ "question": "空しい", "answers": [ "むなしい" ], "comment": "empty; void; vacant\nvain; fruitless; futile; ineffective\nlifeless" },
	{ "question": "穿つ", "answers": [ "うがつ" ], "comment": "to drill; to bore; to pierce; to pass through\nto hit the mark; to get to the heart of (the matter); to be true to (nature)\nto put on; to wear" },
	{ "question": "穿る", "answers": [ "ほじる", "ほじくる" ], "comment": "to dig up; to peck at; to pick (nose, teeth, etc.)\nto pry into; to examine; to dredge up" },
	{ "question": "窄む", "answers": [ "すぼむ", "つぼむ" ], "comment": "to get narrower; to contract\nto close (of flowers); to shut\nto get narrower" },
	{ "question": "窘める", "answers": [ "たしなめる" ], "comment": "to chide; to rebuke; to reprove" },
	{ "question": "窶れる", "answers": [ "やつれる" ], "comment": "to be haggard; to be gaunt; to be emaciated; to be worn out (e.g. illness, worry)" },
	{ "question": "窺う", "answers": [ "うかがう" ], "comment": "to peep (through); to peek; to examine (esp. covertly)\nto await (one's chance)\nto guess; to infer; to gather; to surmise" },
	{ "question": "竦める", "answers": [ "すくめる" ], "comment": "to shrug (shoulders); to duck (head); to draw back (body)" },
	{ "question": "竿", "answers": [ "さお" ], "comment": "rod; pole\nneck (of a shamisen, etc.); shamisen\nbeam (i.e. the crossbar of a balance)\nsingle line (esp. as a flying formation for geese)\npenis\ncounter for flags (on poles); counter for long, thin Japanese sweets (e.g. youkan)\ncounter for poles, rods, etc." },
	{ "question": "笑壺", "answers": [ "えつぼ" ] }, "comment": "laugh; laugh heartily; laugh wholeheartedly; 笑壺に入る" },
	{ "question": "笠", "answers": [ "かさ" ], "comment": "conical hat (East-Asian style); coolie hat\nsomething shaped like a conical hat or an umbrella; shade (of a lamp); mushroom cap; pileus" },
	{ "question": "筈", "answers": [ "はず" ], "comment": "expectation that something took place, will take place or was in some state; it should be so; bound to be; expected to be; must be\nnock (of a bow)\nnock (of an arrow)\nnock-shaped grip (between thumb and forefinger)\nwooden frame on the tip of the mast of a Japanese ship that prevents the hawser from falling out" },
	{ "question": "筏", "answers": [ "いかだ" ], "comment": "raft\nforearm protector\nskewered baby-eel kabayaki" },
	{ "question": "筐体", "answers": [ "きょうたい" ], "comment": "case (of a machine, computer, etc.); casing; housing; enclosure; cabinet; chassis; frame" },
	{ "question": "筑前煮", "answers": [ "ちくぜんに" ], "comment": "chicken stew with taro, carrot, burdock, etc." },
	{ "question": "筵", "answers": [ "むしろ" ], "comment": "woven mat (esp. one made of straw)\nseat" },
	{ "question": "箒", "answers": [ "ほうき" ], "comment": "broom" },
	{ "question": "箪笥", "answers": [ "たんす" ], "comment": "chest of drawers; bureau; cabinet; tansu; dresser" },
	{ "question": "範疇", "answers": [ "はんちゅう" ], "comment": "category" },
	{ "question": "篝火", "answers": [ "かがりび" ], "comment": "fire built in an iron basket (watch fire, fishing fire, etc.); bonfire; campfire\nbrothel-keeper (Edo period)" },
	{ "question": "篤と", "answers": [ "とくと" ], "comment": "carefully; thoroughly; fully; deliberately" },
	{ "question": "篭る", "answers": [ "こもる" ], "comment": "to shut oneself in (e.g. one's room); to be confined in; to seclude oneself; to hide away; to stay inside (one's shell)\nto be filled with (emotion, enthusiasm, etc.)\nto fill the room (of a gas, smell, etc.); to be heavy with (e.g. smoke); to be stuffy; to be dense\nto be muffled (e.g. voice)\nto hold (a castle, fortress, etc.)\nto confine oneself in a temple to pray" },
	{ "question": "簒奪", "answers": [ "さんだつ" ], "comment": "usurpation\nto usurp" },
	{ "question": "簪", "answers": [ "かんざし" ], "comment": "ornate hairpin" },
	{ "question": "籤引き", "answers": [ "くじびき" ], "comment": "lottery; drawn lot" },
	{ "question": "精悍", "answers": [ "せいかん" ], "comment": "virile; tough; masculine; intense" },
	{ "question": "精進", "answers": [ "しょうじん" ], "comment": "concentration; diligence; devotion\nasceticism; zeal in one's quest for enlightenment\nadherence to a vegetarian diet" },
	{ "question": "糊", "answers": [ "のり" ], "comment": "paste; glue\nclothing starch" },
	{ "question": "糊塗", "answers": [ "こと" ], "comment": "covering up; glossing over" },
	{ "question": "糜爛", "answers": [ "びらん" ], "comment": "inflammation; erosion (skin, mucous membranes); ulceration; abscess" },
	{ "question": "納屋", "answers": [ "なや" ], "comment": "shed; barn; outhouse" },
	{ "question": "紐", "answers": [ "ひも" ], "comment": "string; cord\nman who is financially dependent on a woman (such as a gigolo or, in the case of a prostitute, a pimp); pimp" },
	{ "question": "素振り", "answers": [ "そぶり", "すぶり" ], "comment": "behavior; behaviour; manner; attitude; bearing\npractice-swinging (sword, bat, tennis racket, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "絆", "answers": [ "きずな" ], "comment": "bonds (between people); (emotional) ties; relationship; connection; link\ntether; fetters" },
	{ "question": "絆す", "answers": [ "ほだす" ], "comment": "to fetter, to shackle, to bind" },
	{ "question": "絨毯", "answers": [ "じゅうたん" ], "comment": "carpet; rug; runner" },
	{ "question": "継ぎ接ぎ", "answers": [ "つぎはぎ" ], "comment": "patching (clothing); darning\ncobbling together; gathering" },
	{ "question": "綴じる", "answers": [ "とじる" ], "comment": "to bind; to file\nto top with egg (e.g. donburi)" },
	{ "question": "綴る", "answers": [ "つづる" ], "comment": "to spell\nto compose; to frame; to write\nto bind together (e.g. the pages of a book); to sew up; to stitch together; to patch" },
	{ "question": "綺麗", "answers": [ "きれい" ], "comment": "pretty; lovely; beautiful; fair\nclean; clear; pure; tidy; neat\ncompletely; entirely" },
	{ "question": "縋る", "answers": [ "すがる" ], "comment": "to cling to; to hang onto\nto rely on; to depend on\nto implore; to entreat" },
	{ "question": "縛め", "answers": [ "いましめ" ], "comment": "bonds; bondage; binding" },
	{ "question": "縞", "answers": [ "しま" ], "comment": "stripe; bar; streak" },
	{ "question": "縺れ髪", "answers": [ "もつれがみ" ] }, "comment": "tangled, messy hair; unkempt hair" },
	{ "question": "繋ぐ", "answers": [ "つなぐ" ], "comment": "to connect; to link together\nto tie; to fasten; to restrain\nto maintain; to preserve; to keep\nto transfer (phone call); to put a person through\nto hedge; to buy or sell forward" },
	{ "question": "纏まる", "answers": [ "まとまる" ], "comment": "to be collected; to be settled; to be in order" },
	{ "question": "纏める", "answers": [ "まとめる" ], "comment": "to collect; to put (it all) together; to integrate; to consolidate; to unify\nto summarize; to aggregate\nto bring to a conclusion; to finalize; to settle; to put in order\nto establish; to decide" },
	{ "question": "罠", "answers": [ "わな" ], "comment": "snare; trap (for catching wild game, etc.)\ntrap (i.e. ruse, subterfuge, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "翔る", "answers": [ "かける" ], "comment": "to soar; to fly\nto run; to dash" },
	{ "question": "翳す", "answers": [ "かざす" ], "comment": "to hold up over one's head; to hold aloft\nto hold one's hands out (e.g. towards a fire)\nto shade one's eyes, face, etc." },
	{ "question": "老舗", "answers": [ "しにせ", "（ろうほ）" ], "comment": "old shop; shop of long standing\nwell-established; first of the kind; veteran" },
	{ "question": "耄碌", "answers": [ "もうろく" ], "comment": "senility; decrepitude; dotage" },
	{ "question": "耽る", "answers": [ "ふける" ], "comment": "to indulge in; to give oneself up to; to be obsessed by\nto be engrossed in; to be lost in; to be absorbed in" },
	{ "question": "聖", "answers": [ "ひじり" ], "comment": "Saint; St.; S.\nsacred; holy; pure\nhighly virtuous monk\nmonk\nBuddhist solitary\nBuddhist missionary\nsaint (i.e. a virtuous person)\nemperor\nmaster; expert" },
	{ "question": "聡明", "answers": [ "そうめい" ], "comment": "wisdom; sagacity" },
	{ "question": "聳える", "answers": [ "そびえる" ], "comment": "to rise; to tower; to soar" },
	{ "question": "肖る", "answers": [ "あやかる" ], "comment": "to share good luck; to follow (someone's) example\nto be named after" },
	{ "question": "肥沃", "answers": [ "ひよく" ], "comment": "fertile; rich; productive" },
	{ "question": "肴", "answers": [ "さかな" ], "comment": "appetizer or snack served with drinks\nperformance to liven up a bar; conversation to liven up a party" },
	{ "question": "背丈", "answers": [ "せたけ" ], "comment": "stature; height" },
	{ "question": "背凭れ", "answers": [ "せもたれ" ], "comment": "back (of a chair)" },
	{ "question": "背広", "answers": [ "せびろ" ], "comment": "business suit" },
	{ "question": "胡乱", "answers": [ "うろん" ], "comment": "suspicious looking; fishy" },
	{ "question": "胡座", "answers": [ "あぐら" ], "comment": "sitting cross-legged (i.e. Indian style)" },
	{ "question": "胡散臭い", "answers": [ "うさんくさい" ], "comment": "suspicious-looking; shady; questionable; dubious; fishy" },
	{ "question": "胡麻", "answers": [ "ごま" ], "comment": "sesame seeds\nsesame (Sesamum indicum)" },
	{ "question": "脆い", "answers": [ "もろい" ], "comment": "brittle; fragile; tender-hearted" },
	{ "question": "脆弱", "answers": [ "ぜいじゃく" ], "comment": "weak; frail; fragile" },
	{ "question": "脳漿", "answers": [ "のうしょう" ], "comment": "spinal fluid; gray matter; grey matter" },
	{ "question": "腋", "answers": [ "わき" ], "comment": "armpit; under one's arm; side; flank\nbeside; close to; near; by\naside; to the side; away; out of the way\noff-track; off-topic\ndeuteragonist; supporting role\nsecond verse (in a linked series of poems)" },
	{ "question": "膂力", "answers": [ "りょりょく" ], "comment": "physical strength; the strength of one's muscles" },
	{ "question": "膠", "answers": [ "にかわ" ], "comment": "glue (usu. from animal and fish bone, skin, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "膠着", "answers": [ "こうちゃく" ], "comment": "agglutination; adhesion\ndeadlock; stalemate; standstill" },
	{ "question": "膾", "answers": [ "なます" ], "comment": "dish of raw fish and vegetables seasoned in vinegar" },
	{ "question": "膿む", "answers": [ "うむ" ], "comment": "to fester; to form pus" },
	{ "question": "臍", "answers": [ "へそ", "ほぞ" ], "comment": "navel; belly button\nprotrusion or depression in the middle of an object\ncenter; centre; most important part; main point" },
	{ "question": "自嘲", "answers": [ "じちょう" ], "comment": "self-deprecation; self-derision; self-mockery; laughing at oneself" },
	{ "question": "自惚れ", "answers": [ "うぬぼれ" ], "comment": "pretension; conceit; hubris" },
	{ "question": "舐める", "answers": [ "なめる" ], "comment": "to lick\nto taste\nto experience (esp. a hardship)\nto make fun of; to make light of; to put down; to treat with contempt; to underestimate" },
	{ "question": "舫う", "answers": [ "もやう" ], "comment": "to moor (a boat)" },
	{ "question": "舵", "answers": [ "かじ" ], "comment": "rudder; helm" },
	{ "question": "舵取り", "answers": [ "かじとり" ], "comment": "steering; helmsman; coxswain\nguidance; leadership; leader" },
	{ "question": "花押", "answers": [ "かおう" ], "comment": "written seal; stylized signature" },
	{ "question": "花魁", "answers": [ "おいらん" ], "comment": "courtesan; prostitute; oiran" },
	{ "question": "苔", "answers": [ "こけ" ], "comment": "moss\nshort plants resembling moss (incl. other bryophytes, lichens, very small spermatophytes, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "苗床", "answers": [ "なえどこ" ], "comment": "nursery; seedbed; seed-plot" },
	{ "question": "英雄譚", "answers": [ "えいゆうたん" ], "comment": "epic; heroic tale" },
	{ "question": "茶化す", "answers": [ "ちゃかす" ], "comment": "to poke fun at; to make fun of; to send up" },
	{ "question": "茶碗", "answers": [ "ちゃわん" ], "comment": "rice bowl; tea cup; teacup" },
	{ "question": "草臥れる", "answers": [ "くたびれる" ], "comment": "to get tired; to be exhausted\nto wear out; to be battered from long use" },
	{ "question": "荼毘", "answers": [ "だび" ], "comment": "cremation" },
	{ "question": "莫大", "answers": [ "ばくだい" ], "comment": "enormous; vast\nmalva nut (Sterculia lychnophora)" },
	{ "question": "莫迦", "answers": [ "ばか" ], "comment": "fool; idiot\ntrivial matter; folly; absurdity\nfoolish; stupid; dull; absurd; ridiculous\nMactra chinensis (species of trough shell)" },
	{ "question": "菜箸", "answers": [ "さいばし" ], "comment": "long chopsticks (for cooking, serving, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "菩提", "answers": [ "ぼだい" ], "comment": "bodhi; enlightenment\nhappiness in the next world" },
	{ "question": "華奢", "answers": [ "きゃしゃ" ], "comment": "dainty; delicate; slender; slim and elegant\nfragile (e.g. furniture); delicate; frail\nlavish; luxurious; showy; gaudy" },
	{ "question": "萌える", "answers": [ "もえる" ], "comment": "to burst into bud; to sprout\nto have a crush; to be infatuated" },
	{ "question": "萌芽", "answers": [ "ほうが" ], "comment": "germination; germ; sprout; bud; sign" },
	{ "question": "萎びる", "answers": [ "しなびる" ], "comment": "to shrivel (e.g. cut vegetables, skin); to wilt; to fade; to wither; to be wizened" },
	{ "question": "萎む", "answers": [ "しぼむ" ], "comment": "to wither (e.g. flowers, dreams); to sag (e.g. balloon, grapes); to fade (away); to shrivel; to wilt; to deflate" },
	{ "question": "萎れる", "answers": [ "しおれる" ], "comment": "to wither; to wilt; to droop; to fade\nto be dejected; to be disheartened; to be depressed; to be crestfallen" },
	{ "question": "葛藤", "answers": [ "かっとう" ], "comment": "conflict; complication; troubles; discord\nChinese moonseed (Sinomenium acutum)\ncomplex inter-relationship (as in the struggle between two types of vine over one piece of land)" },
	{ "question": "葡萄", "answers": [ "ぶどう" ], "comment": "grape; grapevine" },
	{ "question": "葦", "answers": [ "あし" ], "comment": "common reed (Phragmites australis)" },
	{ "question": "蒔く", "answers": [ "まく" ], "comment": "to sow; to plant; to seed\nto sprinkle (gold or silver powder on lacquerware)" },
	{ "question": "蒙昧", "answers": [ "もうまい" ], "comment": "ignorance; (lack of) enlightenment or civilization (civilisation); unenlightened; uncivilized; uncivilised" },
	{ "question": "蒼い", "answers": [ "あおい" ], "comment": "blue; green\npale\nunripe; inexperienced" },
	{ "question": "蒼穹", "answers": [ "そうきゅう" ], "comment": "blue sky" },
	{ "question": "蓋し", "answers": [ "けだし" ], "comment": "perhaps; probably" },
	{ "question": "蓮", "answers": [ "はす", "はちす" ], "comment": "sacred lotus (Nelumbo nucifera); Indian lotus; lotus\nrose of Sharon (Hibiscus syriacus)" },
	{ "question": "蔓", "answers": [ "つる" ], "comment": "vine; bine; tendril; runner\nbow; temple arm; sidepiece; lug arm; earpiece; part of a pair of glasses that goes over the ear\nconnections; contacts; influence; financial supporter\ncreeping plant; creeper" },
	{ "question": "蔓延", "answers": [ "まんえん" ], "comment": "spread (e.g. of a disease); rampancy; infestation; proliferation; being widespread" },
	{ "question": "蔓延る", "answers": [ "はびこる" ], "comment": "to become overgrown; to grow thick\nto spread; to run rampant; to thrive; to prevail; to become powerful" },
	{ "question": "蔦", "answers": [ "つた" ], "comment": "ivy (esp. Boston ivy, Parthenocissus tricuspidata)" },
	{ "question": "蕎麦", "answers": [ "そば" ], "comment": "buckwheat (Fagopyrum esculentum)\nsoba; Japanese buckwheat noodles" },
	{ "question": "蕩ける", "answers": [ "とろける" ], "comment": "to melt (to a liquid)\nto be enchanted with; to be charmed; to be bewitched" },
	{ "question": "蕾", "answers": [ "つぼみ" ], "comment": "(flower) bud\npromising young person; budding beauty" },
	{ "question": "薬莢", "answers": [ "やっきょう" ], "comment": "(ammunition) cartridge; shell case" },
	{ "question": "藁", "answers": [ "わら" ], "comment": "straw" },
	{ "question": "藪蛇", "answers": [ "やぶへび" ], "comment": "unnecessary trouble brought upon oneself; stirring up a hornet's nest" },
	{ "question": "蘇る", "answers": [ "よみがえる" ], "comment": "to be resurrected; to be resuscitated; to be rehabilitated; to be revived; to be refreshed; to be restored\nto be recalled (e.g. memories); to be brought back" },
	{ "question": "蘇生", "answers": [ "そせい" ], "comment": "rebirth; resuscitation; rehabilitation; reorganization; reorganisation; regeneration; resurrection; reviving" },
	{ "question": "蘊蓄", "answers": [ "うんちく" ], "comment": "great erudition; extensive knowledge; one's vast stock of knowledge" },
	{ "question": "蘭", "answers": [ "らん" ], "comment": "orchid\nHolland; The Netherlands\nJapanese yew (Taxus cuspidata)\nwild rocambole (Allium grayi)\nthoroughwort (species of boneset, Eupatorium fortunei)" },
	{ "question": "虚ろ", "answers": [ "うつろ" ], "comment": "cavity; hollow; void\nhollow (voice); empty (heart); blank (eyes, face, etc.); vacant (stare)" },
	{ "question": "虱潰し", "answers": [ "しらみつぶし" ], "comment": "very thorough search (for contraband, escaped convict, etc.); fine-tooth-comb search; exhaustive search; scouring" },
	{ "question": "蛆", "answers": [ "うじ" ], "comment": "maggot; larva; grub" },
	{ "question": "蛋白質", "answers": [ "たんぱくしつ" ], "comment": "protein" },
	{ "question": "蛸", "answers": [ "たこ" ], "comment": "octopus" },
	{ "question": "蜘蛛", "answers": [ "くも" ], "comment": "spider" },
	{ "question": "蜥蜴", "answers": [ "とかげ" ], "comment": "lizard\nskink lizard (Scincidae spp.)" },
	{ "question": "蝋燭", "answers": [ "ろうそく" ], "comment": "candle" },
	{ "question": "蝙蝠", "answers": [ "こうもり" ], "comment": "bat (Chiroptera spp.)\numbrella\nopportunist; turncoat" },
	{ "question": "蝶", "answers": [ "ちょう" ], "comment": "butterfly" },
	{ "question": "蝶番", "answers": [ "ちょうつがい" ], "comment": "hinge (e.g. on a door)\njoint (esp. an anatomical joint)" },
	{ "question": "蝿", "answers": [ "はえ", "はい" ], "comment": "fly (of infraorder Muscomorpha)\nperson of no worth; pisher; scrub" },
	{ "question": "螺旋", "answers": [ "らせん" ], "comment": "screw\nkey (of a clock, watch, etc.); spring (of a clock, watch, etc.)\nspiral; helix\nscrew" },
	{ "question": "蟒蛇", "answers": [ "うわばみ" ], "comment": "large snake\nheavy drinking; heavy drinker" },
	{ "question": "蟹", "answers": [ "かに" ], "comment": "crab" },
	{ "question": "蠕動", "answers": [ "ぜんどう" ], "comment": "vermiculation; peristalsis; crawling like a worm" },
	{ "question": "蠢く", "answers": [ "うごめく" ], "comment": "to wriggle; to squirm; to crawl like a worm" },
	{ "question": "蠱惑", "answers": [ "こわく" ], "comment": "fascination; glamour; glamor; enchantment; seduction" },
	{ "question": "血漿", "answers": [ "けっしょう" ], "comment": "plasma; blood plasma" },
	{ "question": "血糊", "answers": [ "ちのり" ], "comment": "clotted blood; gore; sticky clots of blood" },
	{ "question": "衒い", "answers": [ "てらい" ], "comment": "affectation; pretension" },
	{ "question": "衝く", "answers": [ "つく" ], "comment": "to prick; to stab\nto poke; to prod; to push; to thrust; to nudge; to hit; to strike\nto use (a cane); to prop oneself up with; to press against (the floor, etc.)\nto attack\nto brave (the rain, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "袂", "answers": [ "たもと" ], "comment": "sleeve (esp. of a kimono); pocket of sleeve\nvicinity (esp. of a bridge)\nfoot of a mountain; base of a mountain" },
	{ "question": "袈裟斬り", "answers": [ "けさぎり" ], "comment": "slashing a sword diagonally from the shoulder" },
	{ "question": "被曝", "answers": [ "ひばく" ], "comment": "being exposed to radiation; radiation exposure" },
	{ "question": "裂帛", "answers": [ "れっぱく" ], "comment": "cutting through cloth; sound of cutting through cloth\nshrieking sound; woman's scream; loud scream\ncry of the lesser cuckoo (Cuculus poliocephalus)" },
	{ "question": "襖", "answers": [ "ふすま" ], "comment": "fusuma; Japanese sliding screen\neveryday garment worn by men in ancient Japan" },
	{ "question": "見窄らしい", "answers": [ "みすぼらしい" ], "comment": "shabby; seedy" },
	{ "question": "覗く", "answers": [ "のぞく" ], "comment": "to peek (though a keyhole, gap, etc.)\nto look down into (a ravine, etc.)\nto peek into (a shop, bookstore, etc.)\nto sneak a look at; to take a quick look at\nto peep (through a telescope, microscope, etc.)\nto stick out (a scarf from a collar, etc.); to peek through (sky through a forest canopy, etc.)\nto examine (an expression); to study (a face)\nto face" },
	{ "question": "覚束ない", "answers": [ "おぼつかない" ], "comment": "uncertain; doubtful\nunreliable; unsteady; shaky; faltering" },
	{ "question": "解す", "answers": [ "ほぐす", "ほごす", "かいす" ], "comment": "to unravel; to untie; to untangle; to loosen\nto break into small pieces (of fish, meat, etc.)\nto relax; to ease\nto understand; to comprehend\nto understand; to appreciate\nto interpret" },
	{ "question": "言い種", "answers": [ "いいぐさ" ], "comment": "remarks; comments\nway of talking; speaking style\nexcuse\ntopic (of conversation)" },
	{ "question": "言祝ぐ", "answers": [ "ことほぐ" ], "comment": "to congratulate; to wish (someone) well; to celebrate" },
	{ "question": "訊く", "answers": [ "きく" ], "comment": "to hear\nto listen (e.g. to music)\nto ask; to enquire; to query\nto learn of; to hear about\nto follow (advice); to comply with" },
	{ "question": "訊ねる", "answers": [ "たずねる" ], "comment": "to ask; to enquire; to inquire\nto search; to look for; to look into; to investigate" },
	{ "question": "訝しい", "answers": [ "いぶかしい" ], "comment": "suspicious; doubtful" },
	{ "question": "訝る", "answers": [ "いぶかる" ], "comment": "to wonder; to puzzle oneself about; to feel anxious about; to suspect" },
	{ "question": "訥々と", "answers": [ "とつとつと" ], "comment": "haltingly; falteringly" },
	{ "question": "訥弁", "answers": [ "とつべん" ], "comment": "slowness of speech; awkwardness of speech" },
	{ "question": "設える", "answers": [ "しつらえる" ], "comment": "to provide; to arrange; to install" },
	{ "question": "証", "answers": [ "あかし" ], "comment": "proof (e.g. of love, of innocence); evidence; testimony; vindication (of innocence)\nlicense; membership card; permit\nto testify (usu. Christian religious context)" },
	{ "question": "詫びる", "answers": [ "わびる" ], "comment": "to apologize; to apologise" },
	{ "question": "詰る", "answers": [ "なじる" ], "comment": "to rebuke; to scold; to tell off" },
	{ "question": "詳らか", "answers": [ "つまびらか" ], "comment": "detailed; clear" },
	{ "question": "読本", "answers": [ "とくほん" ], "comment": "reading-book; reader; guidebook; manual\ntextbook (esp. a pre-war elementary school Japanese language textbook)\ntype of popular literature from the late Edo period" },
	{ "question": "読点", "answers": [ "とうてん" ], "comment": "comma" },
	{ "question": "誰何", "answers": [ "すいか" ], "comment": "challenging (an unknown person); asking a person's identity" },
	{ "question": "誰某", "answers": [ "たれがし", "だれそれ", "たれぼう" ], "comment": "a certain someone; Mr So-and-so" },
	{ "question": "誹謗", "answers": [ "ひぼう" ], "comment": "slander; abuse" },
	{ "question": "誼み", "answers": [ "よしみ" ], "comment": "friendship; friendly relations; connection; relation; intimacy" },
	{ "question": "諌める", "answers": [ "いさめる" ], "comment": "to remonstrate; to admonish (someone) for; to advise (someone) not to; to warn against" },
	{ "question": "諍い", "answers": [ "いさかい" ], "comment": "quarrel; dispute; argument" },
	{ "question": "諜報", "answers": [ "ちょうほう" ], "comment": "secret information; intelligence" },
	{ "question": "諳んじる", "answers": [ "そらんじる" ], "comment": "to memorize; to memorise; to recite from memory" },
	{ "question": "諺", "answers": [ "ことわざ" ], "comment": "proverb; maxim" },
	{ "question": "謁見", "answers": [ "えっけん" ], "comment": "audience (with a superior, e.g. nobility)" },
	{ "question": "謗る", "answers": [ "そしる" ], "comment": "to slander; to libel; to criticize; to criticise" },
	{ "question": "謙る", "answers": [ "へりくだる" ], "comment": "to deprecate oneself and praise the listener; to abase oneself" },
	{ "question": "謙遜", "answers": [ "けんそん" ], "comment": "modesty; humility; being humble" },
	{ "question": "謳う", "answers": [ "うたう" ], "comment": "to extol; to sing the praises of; to celebrate\nto declare; to stipulate; to express; to state; to insist" },
	{ "question": "謳歌", "answers": [ "おうか" ], "comment": "rejoicing; glorification; exultation; celebration; enjoyment; singing praises" },
	{ "question": "譫言", "answers": [ "うわごと" ], "comment": "talking in delirium; incoherent muttering\nnonsense; bullshit; silly things; joke" },
	{ "question": "象る", "answers": [ "かたどる" ], "comment": "to model on; to make in the shape of; to represent; to pattern after; to imitate\nto symbolise" },
	{ "question": "豪酒", "answers": [ "ごうしゅ" ], "comment": "heavy [hard] drinking" },
	{ "question": "豹変", "answers": [ "ひょうへん" ], "comment": "sudden change; complete change" },
	{ "question": "貫禄", "answers": [ "かんろく" ], "comment": "presence; dignity" },
	{ "question": "貰う", "answers": [ "もらう" ], "comment": "to receive; to take; to accept\nto get somebody to do something" },
	{ "question": "貶す", "answers": [ "けなす" ], "comment": "to speak ill of; to disparage" },
	{ "question": "貶める", "answers": [ "おとしめる" ], "comment": "to show contempt for; to look down upon; to have a low opinion of\nto cause to fall; to make decline" },
	{ "question": "賑やか", "answers": [ "にぎやか" ], "comment": "bustling; busy; lively" },
	{ "question": "賑わう", "answers": [ "にぎわう" ], "comment": "to be crowded with people; to be bustling with\nto prosper; to flourish; to do thriving business" },
	{ "question": "賢しら", "answers": [ "さかしら" ], "comment": "impertinent" },
	{ "question": "賤しい", "answers": [ "いやしい" ], "comment": "lowborn; humble; lowly\nvulgar; coarse; crude; mean; base; vile\nshabby\ngreedy; gluttonous; avaricious" },
	{ "question": "賭博", "answers": [ "とばく" ], "comment": "gambling" },
	{ "question": "賽銭", "answers": [ "さいせん" ], "comment": "monetary offering; offertory" },
	{ "question": "贅沢", "answers": [ "ぜいたく" ], "comment": "luxury; extravagance\nto live in luxury; to indulge oneself\nlavish (use of something); abundant; copious; wasteful" },
	{ "question": "贋造", "answers": [ "がんぞう" ], "comment": "counterfeiting; forgery; fabrication" },
	{ "question": "贖う", "answers": [ "あがなう" ], "comment": "to atone for; to expiate; to redeem; to make up for; to compensate for" },
	{ "question": "赤提灯", "answers": [ "あかちょうちん" ], "comment": "red paper restaurant lantern\ncheap eating and drinking place" },
	{ "question": "足掻く", "answers": [ "あがく" ], "comment": "to paw (at) the ground\nto flounder; to struggle" },
	{ "question": "足繁く", "answers": [ "あししげく" ], "comment": "frequently" },
	{ "question": "跋扈", "answers": [ "ばっこ" ], "comment": "rampancy; prevalence; domination" },
	{ "question": "跨がる", "answers": [ "またがる" ], "comment": "to extend over; to extend into\nto straddle" },
	{ "question": "跨ぐ", "answers": [ "またぐ" ], "comment": "to step over; to step across; to stride over; to stride across; to cross\nto stretch over; to span; to bridge; to saddle; to straddle" },
	{ "question": "跪く", "answers": [ "ひざまずく", "ひざまづく" ], "comment": "to kneel" },
	{ "question": "踵", "answers": [ "かかと", "きびす" ], "comment": "heel (of foot, shoe, stocking, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "蹂躙", "answers": [ "じゅうりん" ], "comment": "trampling down; overrunning; infringement; violation" },
	{ "question": "蹄", "answers": [ "ひづめ" ], "comment": "hoof" },
	{ "question": "蹲る", "answers": [ "うずくまる", "つくばる" ], "comment": "to crouch; to squat; to cower" },
	{ "question": "躊躇", "answers": [ "ちゅうちょ" ], "comment": "hesitation; indecision; vacillation" },
	{ "question": "躊躇う", "answers": [ "ためらう" ], "comment": "to hesitate; to waver" },
	{ "question": "躓く", "answers": [ "つまずく", "つまづく" ], "comment": "to stumble; to trip\nto fail" },
	{ "question": "身動ぐ", "answers": [ "みじろぐ" ], "comment": "to stir; to move" },
	{ "question": "躾", "answers": [ "しつけ" ], "comment": "discipline; training; teaching manners" },
	{ "question": "軋む", "answers": [ "きしむ" ], "comment": "to jar; to creak; to grate" },
	{ "question": "軋轢", "answers": [ "あつれき" ], "comment": "friction; discord; strife" },
	{ "question": "軟膏", "answers": [ "なんこう" ], "comment": "ointment; salve" },
	{ "question": "轍", "answers": [ "わだち", "てつ" ], "comment": "rut; wheel track; furrow" },
	{ "question": "轡", "answers": [ "くつわ" ], "comment": "bit (i.e. attached to a bridle)" },
	{ "question": "轢く", "answers": [ "ひく" ], "comment": "to run over (with a vehicle); to knock down" },
	{ "question": "辟易", "answers": [ "へきえき" ], "comment": "to be stumped; to be nonplussed; to be disconcerted; to dumbfounded\nto be fed up with; to be tired of; to find unable to bear\nto wince; to shrink back; to cringe" },
	{ "question": "辻褄", "answers": [ "つじつま" ], "comment": "coherence; consistency" },
	{ "question": "辿る", "answers": [ "たどる" ], "comment": "to follow (road); to pursue (course); to follow up; to follow (hyperlink)" },
	{ "question": "迂闊", "answers": [ "うかつ" ], "comment": "careless; stupid; thoughtless; heedless; unobservant; inadvertant; incautious" },
	{ "question": "迸る", "answers": [ "ほとばしる", "とばしる" ], "comment": "to surge; to well up; to gush out" },
	{ "question": "逆鱗", "answers": [ "げきりん" ], "comment": "imperial wrath; one's superior's anger" },
	{ "question": "透かさず", "answers": [ "すかさず" ], "comment": "without a moment's delay" },
	{ "question": "這う", "answers": [ "はう" ], "comment": "to creep; to crawl" },
	{ "question": "逞しい", "answers": [ "たくましい" ], "comment": "burly; strong; sturdy\nindomitable; indefatigable; strong-willed; resolute; bold\nrobust (vitality, appetite, economic growth, etc.); strong" },
	{ "question": "逡巡", "answers": [ "しゅんじゅん" ], "comment": "hesitation; indecision" },
	{ "question": "逢引", "answers": [ "あいびき" ], "comment": "(secret) date; clandestine meeting; assignation; tryst; rendezvous" },
	{ "question": "逢瀬", "answers": [ "おうせ" ], "comment": "rendezvous; tryst; (lover's) meeting; (secret) date" },
	{ "question": "遍く", "answers": [ "あまねく" ], "comment": "widely; generally; universally; far and wide" },
	{ "question": "遡行", "answers": [ "そこう" ], "comment": "going upstream; sailing against the current" },
	{ "question": "遣る", "answers": [ "やる" ], "comment": "to do; to undertake; to perform; to play (a game); to study\nto send; to dispatch; to despatch\nto put; to move; to turn (one's head, glance, etc.)\nto give (esp. to someone of equal or lower status); to let have; to present; to bestow; to confer\nto make (a vehicle) go faster\nto run (a business); to keep; to be engaged in; to practice (law, medicine, etc.); to practise\nto have (food, drink, etc.); to eat; to drink; to smoke\nto hold (a performance); to perform; to show\nto ease (one's mind)\nto harm; to injure; to kill\nto have sex with\nto live; to get by; to get along\nto do ... completely\nto do ... broadly; to do ... to a great distance\nto do ... for (someone of equal or lower status); to do ... to (sometimes with negative nuance)\nto make active efforts to ..." },
	{ "question": "遥か", "answers": [ "はるか" ], "comment": "far; far away; distant; remote; far off" },
	{ "question": "遮蔽", "answers": [ "しゃへい" ], "comment": "shielding; sheltering; screening; shading; masking" },
	{ "question": "遵守", "answers": [ "じゅんしゅ" ], "comment": "compliance; adherence (to a set of rules); (religious) observance" },
	{ "question": "邁進", "answers": [ "まいしん" ], "comment": "pushing forward (undaunted, bravely); working vigorously towards an aim; struggling on; striving towards" },
	{ "question": "邂逅", "answers": [ "かいこう" ], "comment": "chance meeting" },
	{ "question": "鄙びる", "answers": [ "ひなびる" ], "comment": "to become rustic; to be countrified" },
	{ "question": "醍醐味", "answers": [ "だいごみ" ], "comment": "the real pleasure (of something); the real thrill; the true charm\nflavour of ghee; delicious taste\nBuddha's gracious teachings" },
	{ "question": "醤油", "answers": [ "しょうゆ" ], "comment": "soy sauce; shoyu" },
	{ "question": "釉薬", "answers": [ "ゆうやく", "うわぐすり" ], "comment": "glaze; overglaze; enamel" },
	{ "question": "野次馬根性", "answers": [ "やじうまこんじょう" ], "comment": "the spirit of curiosity" },
	{ "question": "金槌", "answers": [ "かなづち" ], "comment": "hammer\nhopeless swimmer; complete beginner at swimming; someone who sinks like a stone" },
	{ "question": "釘", "answers": [ "くぎ" ], "comment": "nail (i.e. small metal spike)" },
	{ "question": "鈍色", "answers": [ "にびいろ" ], "comment": "dark gray; dark grey" },
	{ "question": "鉄桶", "answers": [ "てっとう" ] }, "comment": "iron bucket" },
	{ "question": "鉄槌", "answers": [ "てっつい" ], "comment": "iron hammer\ncrushing blow" },
	{ "question": "銛", "answers": [ "もり" ], "comment": "lance; harpoon" },
	{ "question": "鋏", "answers": [ "はさみ", "やっとこ" ], "comment": "scissors; shears; clippers\nhole punch\npincers; nippers; pliers" },
	{ "question": "鋤", "answers": [ "すき" ], "comment": "spade\nplough; plow" },
	{ "question": "鋸", "answers": [ "のこぎり" ], "comment": "saw\nmusical saw" },
	{ "question": "錆", "answers": [ "さび" ], "comment": "rust" },
	{ "question": "錆びる", "answers": [ "さびる" ], "comment": "to rust; to become rusty" },
	{ "question": "錨", "answers": [ "いかり" ], "comment": "anchor" },
	{ "question": "錫", "answers": [ "すず" ], "comment": "tin (Sn)" },
	{ "question": "鏃", "answers": [ "やじり" ], "comment": "arrowhead" },
	{ "question": "鏖殺", "answers": [ "おうさつ" ], "comment": "massacre; extermination" },
	{ "question": "長閑", "answers": [ "のどか" ], "comment": "tranquil; calm; quiet; peaceful" },
	{ "question": "閂", "answers": [ "かんぬき" ], "comment": "bar; bolt (e.g. on door); latch" },
	{ "question": "閃く", "answers": [ "ひらめく" ], "comment": "to flash (lightning, etc.); to flicker (lights); to glitter\nto wave; to undulate\nto hit on a good idea; to occur to someone" },
	{ "question": "閃光", "answers": [ "せんこう" ], "comment": "flash; glint" },
	{ "question": "開墾", "answers": [ "かいこん" ], "comment": "cultivating new land; clearing; reclamation" },
	{ "question": "間隙", "answers": [ "かんげき" ], "comment": "gap" },
	{ "question": "闊歩", "answers": [ "かっぽ" ], "comment": "striding; swaggering; strutting\nlording it over others; acting as though one owns the place; throwing one's weight around" },
	{ "question": "阿呆", "answers": [ "あほう", "あほ" ], "comment": "fool; simpleton; idiot" },
	{ "question": "隈なく", "answers": [ "くまなく" ], "comment": "all over; everywhere; in every nook and cranny" },
	{ "question": "隘路", "answers": [ "あいろ" ], "comment": "defile; narrow path\nbottleneck; impasse" },
	{ "question": "隙", "answers": [ "すき" ], "comment": "gap; space\nbreak; interlude; interval\nchink (in one's armor, armour); chance; opportunity; weak spot\nbreach (of a relationship between people)" },
	{ "question": "隠れ蓑", "answers": [ "かくれみの" ], "comment": "cover; front (e.g. for illegal activities); magic cloak of invisibility\nDendropanax trifidus (species of flowering plant)" },
	{ "question": "隠棲", "answers": [ "いんせい" ], "comment": "secluded life" },
	{ "question": "隠蔽", "answers": [ "いんぺい" ], "comment": "concealment; suppression; hiding" },
	{ "question": "隻手", "answers": [ "せきしゅ" ], "comment": "one arm; one hand" },
	{ "question": "隻眼", "answers": [ "せきがん" ], "comment": "eye (for pictures, etc.); one eye" },
	{ "question": "雀", "answers": [ "すずめ" ], "comment": "tree sparrow (Passer montanus)\ntalkative person; knowledgeable person" },
	{ "question": "雁字搦め", "answers": [ "がんじがらめ" ], "comment": "bound hand and foot; hedged in (e.g. by restrictions); immobile" },
	{ "question": "雑魚", "answers": [ "ざこ" ], "comment": "small fish; small fry\nperson of low social standing" },
	{ "question": "雛", "answers": [ "ひな", "ひよこ", "ひよっこ" ], "comment": "young bird; chick\nhina doll; doll displayed during the Girls' Festival\ngreen; wet behind the ears; juvenile" },
	{ "question": "雨樋", "answers": [ "あまどい" ], "comment": "drainspout; rain gutter" },
	{ "question": "雪ぐ", "answers": [ "すすぐ", "そそぐ" ], "comment": "to rinse; to wash out\nto have one's revenge; to wipe out a disgrace" },
	{ "question": "雪崩", "answers": [ "なだれ" ], "comment": "avalanche; snowslide" },
	{ "question": "雫", "answers": [ "しずく" ], "comment": "drop (of water); drip" },
	{ "question": "雹", "answers": [ "ひょう" ], "comment": "hail (esp. hailballs 5 mm or greater)" },
	{ "question": "霊廟", "answers": [ "れいびょう" ], "comment": "mausoleum" },
	{ "question": "霞む", "answers": [ "かすむ" ], "comment": "to become misty; to become hazy\nto get blurry; to grow dim\nto be overshadowed; to be upstaged; to be outshone" },
	{ "question": "靄", "answers": [ "もや" ], "comment": "mist; haze" },
	{ "question": "静脈", "answers": [ "じょうみゃく" ], "comment": "vein" },
	{ "question": "静謐", "answers": [ "せいひつ" ], "comment": "peacefulness (esp. the world); tranquillity; tranquility" },
	{ "question": "靡く", "answers": [ "なびく" ], "comment": "to bend; to flutter; to wave\nto yield to; to be swayed by; to bow to; to obey" },
	{ "question": "面皰", "answers": [ "にきび", "めんぽう" ], "comment": "pimple; acne" },
	{ "question": "革まる", "answers": [ "あらたまる" ], "comment": "to be renewed\nto stand on ceremony; to be formal\nto take a turn for the worse" },
	{ "question": "鞍", "answers": [ "くら" ], "comment": "saddle" },
	{ "question": "鞘", "answers": [ "さや" ], "comment": "scabbard; sheath\ncap (on pen, brush, etc.); case; sleeve\nmargin (between two prices); spread; markup; commission\nenclosure; outer fence" },
	{ "question": "韜晦", "answers": [ "とうかい" ], "comment": "hidden (talents, etc.); self-concealment; self-effacement" },
	{ "question": "頑な", "answers": [ "かたくな" ], "comment": "obstinate; stubborn; mulish; die-hard; bigoted" },
	{ "question": "頷く", "answers": [ "うなずく", "うなづく" ], "comment": "to nod; to bow one's head in assent; to agree" },
	{ "question": "類い稀", "answers": [ "たぐいまれ" ], "comment": "unique; rare; exceptional; unparalleled; incomparable" },
	{ "question": "顰める", "answers": [ "ひそめる", "しかめる" ], "comment": "to pull a wry face; to screw one's face up; to pucker one's face; to scowl; to grimace; to frown\nto knit (one's eyebrows)" },
	{ "question": "颯爽", "answers": [ "さっそう" ], "comment": "gallant; dashing; jaunty" },
	{ "question": "飛沫", "answers": [ "しぶき", "ひまつ" ], "comment": "splash; spray\nsplash; spray" },
	{ "question": "飛翔", "answers": [ "ひしょう" ], "comment": "flight; flying; soaring" },
	{ "question": "食む", "answers": [ "はむ" ], "comment": "to eat (fodder, grass, etc.)\nto receive (a salary); to receive a stipend from one's lord" },
	{ "question": "飢饉", "answers": [ "ききん" ], "comment": "famine; drought; shortage; crop failure" },
	{ "question": "飯事", "answers": [ "ままごと" ], "comment": "playing house" },
	{ "question": "飯櫃", "answers": [ "めしびつ", "いいびつ" ], "comment": "round, wooden container for cooked rice" },
	{ "question": "飯盒", "answers": [ "はんごう" ], "comment": "(soldier's) cooking utensils; mess kit\noutdoor (camping) cooking utensils" },
	{ "question": "飴", "answers": [ "あめ" ], "comment": "(hard) candy; toffee\nrice-sugar; sugar made from the starch of rice, potatoes, etc.\namber; yellowish-brown\nconfection (e.g. candy, mochi); sweet" },
	{ "question": "飴玉", "answers": [ "あめだま" ], "comment": "candy" },
	{ "question": "餌", "answers": [ "えさ", "え" ], "comment": "(animal) feed; fodder; pet food\nbait; lure; enticement" },
	{ "question": "餌食", "answers": [ "えじき" ], "comment": "prey; victim" },
	{ "question": "饒舌", "answers": [ "じょうぜつ" ], "comment": "garrulity; loquacity; talkativeness" },
	{ "question": "馬蹄", "answers": [ "ばてい" ], "comment": "horse's hooves" },
	{ "question": "馳せ参じる", "answers": [ "はせさんじる" ], "comment": "to hasten to join; to hurry to visit" },
	{ "question": "馴らす", "answers": [ "ならす" ], "comment": "to accustom; to train (e.g. one's ear)\nto tame; to domesticate; to train (e.g. an animal)" },
	{ "question": "馴れ馴れしい", "answers": [ "なれなれしい" ], "comment": "over-familiar" },
	{ "question": "馴染む", "answers": [ "なじむ" ], "comment": "to become familiar with; to fit in; to adapt oneself; to get used to; to grow accustomed to" },
	{ "question": "馴致", "answers": [ "じゅんち" ], "comment": "taming; gradual habituation; leading to" },
	{ "question": "駒", "answers": [ "こま" ], "comment": "piece (in shogi, chess, etc.)\nhorse; foal\nbridge (of a violin, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "駿足", "answers": [ "しゅんそく" ], "comment": "fast runner\nswift horse; fleet steed" },
	{ "question": "騙す", "answers": [ "だます" ], "comment": "to trick; to cheat; to deceive\nto coax; to wheedle; to soothe and humor (humour)" },
	{ "question": "驕る", "answers": [ "おごる" ], "comment": "to give (someone) a treat\nto be extravagant; to live luxuriously\nto be proud; to be haughty" },
	{ "question": "驚愕", "answers": [ "きょうがく" ], "comment": "surprise; fright; shock; amazement; astonishment" },
	{ "question": "骨董品", "answers": [ "こっとうひん" ], "comment": "curio; antique" },
	{ "question": "骸骨", "answers": [ "がいこつ" ], "comment": "skeleton" },
	{ "question": "高嶺の花", "answers": [ "たかねのはな" ], "comment": "goal which is unattainable; prize beyond one's reach; woman who is out of one's league; flower on a high peak" },
	{ "question": "髭", "answers": [ "ひげ" ], "comment": "moustache; beard; whiskers\nextremely short pulse appearing on an electrical signal" },
	{ "question": "魚市場", "answers": [ "うおいちば" ], "comment": "fish market" },
	{ "question": "鮭", "answers": [ "さけ", "しゃけ" ], "comment": "salmon (Salmonidae spp.)\nchum salmon (Oncorhynchus keta)" },
	{ "question": "鯉", "answers": [ "こい" ], "comment": "common carp (Cyprinus carpio); koi carp" },
	{ "question": "鯱張る", "answers": [ "しゃちほこばる", "しゃちこばる", "しゃっちょこばる", "しゃちばる" ], "comment": "to stand on ceremony\nto stiffen up (the nerves); to be tense" },
	{ "question": "鰓", "answers": [ "えら" ], "comment": "gills; branchia\nangle of the mandible; gonial angle" },
	{ "question": "鰭", "answers": [ "ひれ", "はた" ], "comment": "fin (e.g. of a fish)" },
	{ "question": "鱗", "answers": [ "うろこ" ], "comment": "scale (of fish, snake, etc.)\nserif (on kana or kanji (e.g. in Mincho font))" },
	{ "question": "鳥居", "answers": [ "とりい" ], "comment": "torii; Shinto shrine archway" },
	{ "question": "鳩尾", "answers": [ "みずおち", "みぞおち" ], "comment": "pit of the stomach; solar plexus" },
	{ "question": "鳳凰", "answers": [ "ほうおう" ], "comment": "Chinese firebird; Chinese phoenix" },
	{ "question": "鴨", "answers": [ "かも" ], "comment": "duck\neasy mark; sucker; sitting duck" },
	{ "question": "鵜呑み", "answers": [ "うのみ" ], "comment": "swallowing (food, story)" },
	{ "question": "鵞鳥", "answers": [ "がちょう" ], "comment": "goose" },
	{ "question": "鷲", "answers": [ "わし" ], "comment": "eagle (Accipitridae family)" },
	{ "question": "鷲掴み", "answers": [ "わしづかみ" ], "comment": "grabbing hold; eagle grip; tight hold" },
	{ "question": "鷹", "answers": [ "たか" ], "comment": "falcon (Falconidae spp.); hawk" },
	{ "question": "鷹揚", "answers": [ "おうよう" ], "comment": "largehearted; generous\nplacid; composed; cool; collected" },
	{ "question": "麝香", "answers": [ "じゃこう" ], "comment": "musk" },
	{ "question": "麻痺", "answers": [ "まひ" ], "comment": "paralysis; palsy; numbness; stupor" },
	{ "question": "黄泉", "answers": [ "よみ" ], "comment": "underground spring\nHades; hell; underworld" },
	{ "question": "黎明", "answers": [ "れいめい" ], "comment": "daybreak; dawn; gray of the morning (grey)\ndawn (of a new age)" },
	{ "question": "鼻梁", "answers": [ "びりょう" ], "comment": "bridge of the nose" },
	{ "question": "鼾", "answers": [ "いびき" ], "comment": "snoring; snore" },
	{ "question": "齎す", "answers": [ "もたらす" ], "comment": "to bring; to take; to bring about" },
	{ "question": "齟齬", "answers": [ "そご" ], "comment": "inconsistency; discord; conflict; discrepancy; contradiction; failure; frustration" },
	{ "question": "齢", "answers": [ "よわい" ], "comment": "(one's) age\ninstar" },
	{ "question": "齧り付く", "answers": [ "かぶりつく", "かじりつく" ], "comment": "to bite into; to sink one's teeth into\nto stick to; to cling to; to hold on to" },
	{ "question": "齧る", "answers": [ "かじる" ], "comment": "to gnaw; to nibble; to bite; to munch; to crunch\nto dabble in; to have a smattering of" },
	{ "question": "恰幅", "answers": [ "かっぷく" ], "comment": "physique; bodily build" },
	{ "question": "捕吏", "answers": [ "ほり" ], "comment": "constable; policeman" },
	{ "question": "下吏", "answers": [ "かり" ], "comment": "lower official" },
	{ "question": "微か", "answers": [ "かすか" ], "comment": "faint; dim; weak; slight; vague; indistinct; hazy\npoor; wretched; meagre; meager; scanty" },
	{ "question": "奔る", "answers": [ "はしる" ], "comment": " to run\nto travel (movement of vehicles); to drive\nto hurry to\nto retreat (from battle); to take flight\nto run away from home\nto elope\nto flash; to streak; to shoot through (e.g. pain)" },
	{ "question": "過る", "answers": [ "よぎる" ], "comment": "to go by; to cross; to pass by; to float across" },
	{ "question": "齧歯類", "answers": [ "げっしるい" ], "comment": "rodent" },
	{ "question": "以て", "answers": [ "もって" ], "comment": "with; by\nby means of; because; in view of" },
	{ "question": "可笑しい", "answers": [ "おかしい" ], "comment": "funny; amusing; comical; laughable; ridiculous\nstrange; odd; funny; peculiar; weird; unusual; eccentric\nimproper; unsuitable; unbecoming\nsuspicious" },
	{ "question": "足袋", "answers": [ "たび" ], "comment": "tabi; Japanese socks (with split toe)" },
	{ "question": "清む", "answers": [ "すむ" ], "comment": "to clear (e.g. weather); to become transparent" },
	{ "question": "刷毛", "answers": [ "はけ" ], "comment": "brush (e.g. for painting, basting, etc.); whisk" },
	{ "question": "斜交い", "answers": [ "はすかい" ], "comment": "aslant; oblique; diagonal; askew; cater-cornered; catty-cornered" },
	{ "question": "唯", "answers": [ "ただ" ], "comment": "ordinary; common; usual\nfree of charge\nunaffected; as is; safe\nonly; merely; just; simply\nbut; however; nevertheless" },
	{ "question": "気障", "answers": [ "きざ" ], "comment": "affected; smug; pompous; conceited; snobby; pretentious" },
	{ "question": "舅", "answers": [ "しゅうと" ], "comment": "father-in-law" },
	{ "question": "生温い", "answers": [ "なまぬるい" ], "comment": "lukewarm; tepid\nhalf-hearted; vague; weak\nlenient; mild; soft" },
	{ "question": "温い", "answers": [ "ぬるい" ], "comment": "lukewarm; tepid\nlenient\nslow; stupid" },
	{ "question": "為す", "answers": [ "なす" ], "comment": "to build up; to establish\nto form; to become (a state)\nto accomplish; to achieve; to succeed in\nto change into\nto do; to perform\nto intend to; to attempt; to try" },
	{ "question": "顰蹙", "answers": [ "ひんしゅく" ], "comment": "【１級】\nfrowning on; looking on with scorn; showing disapproval" },
	{ "question": "麦芽", "answers": [ "ばくが" ], "comment": "malt" },
	{ "question": "角錐", "answers": [ "かくすい" ], "comment": "pyramid" },
	{ "question": "高騰", "answers": [ "こうとう" ], "comment": "sudden price jump; steep price rise" },
	{ "question": "掠奪", "answers": [ "りゃくだつ" ], "comment": "pillage; plunder; looting; robbery" },
	{ "question": "吐瀉", "answers": [ "としゃ" ], "comment": "vomiting and diarrhea (diarrhoea)" },
	{ "question": "誂える", "answers": [ "あつらえる" ], "comment": "to give an order; to place an order" },
	{ "question": "拵える", "answers": [ "こしらえる" ], "comment": "to make; to manufacture" },
	{ "question": "唯々諾々", "answers": [ "いいだくだく" ], "comment": "quite willingly; readily; with acquiescence" },
	{ "question": "奔走", "answers": [ "ほんそう" ], "comment": "running about; making every effort; being busily engaged (in something); good offices" },
	{ "question": "翻弄", "answers": [ "ほんろう" ], "comment": "trifling with; toying with; playing with; making sport of; making fun of; leading around by the nose\ntossing about (a ship)" },
	{ "question": "攪拌", "answers": [ "かくはん" ], "comment": "agitation; stirring; whipping; beating" },
	{ "question": "覿面", "answers": [ "てきめん" ], "comment": "immediacy; instantaneousness; promptness" },
	{ "question": "鐙", "answers": [ "あぶみ" ], "comment": "stirrup" },
	{ "question": "鎖帷子", "answers": [ "くさりかたびら" ], "comment": "chain mail (armor, armour)" },
	{ "question": "寂寥", "answers": [ "せきりょう" ], "comment": "loneliness; desolateness" },
	{ "question": "沽券", "answers": [ "こけん" ], "comment": "dignity; credit; public estimation; face; honor; reputation\ndeed of sale (for a land, forest or house)\nsale value; selling price\ncertificate of sale; deed of sale" },
	{ "question": "哀悼", "answers": [ "あいとう" ], "comment": "condolence; regret; tribute; sorrow; sympathy; lament" },
	{ "question": "弔慰", "answers": [ "ちょうい" ], "comment": "condolence; sympathy; mourning" },
	{ "question": "釣果", "answers": [ "ちょうか" ], "comment": "catch (fishing); amount of fish caught; caught fish" },
	{ "question": "遺言", "answers": [ "ゆいごん" ], "comment": "will, testament" },
	{ "question": "潰走", "answers": [ "かいそう" ], "comment": "rout; stampede" },
	{ "question": "鹵獲", "answers": [ "ろかく" ], "comment": "capture; seizure; plunder" },
	{ "question": "遁走", "answers": [ "とんそう" ], "comment": "fleeing; escape" },
	{ "question": "鉋", "answers": [ "かんな" ], "comment": "plane (for working with wood)" },
	{ "question": "趨勢", "answers": [ "すうせい" ], "comment": "tendency; trend" },
	{ "question": "撥水", "answers": [ "はっすい" ], "comment": "water repellency" },
	{ "question": "叡智", "answers": [ "えいち" ], "comment": "wisdom; intelligence; intellect" },
	{ "question": "寛恕", "answers": [ "かんじょ" ], "comment": "magnanimity; forgiveness; generosity" },
	{ "question": "剴切", "answers": [ "がいせつ" ], "comment": "appropriateness; adequacy; aptness; relevance" },
	{ "question": "約款", "answers": [ "やっかん" ], "comment": "agreement; stipulation; article; clause" },
	{ "question": "斟酌", "answers": [ "しんしゃく" ], "comment": "consideration (for others); (making) allowance" },
	{ "question": "悋気", "answers": [ "りんき" ], "comment": "jealousy" },
	{ "question": "祠", "answers": [ "ほこら" ], "comment": "hokora; small wayside shrine" },
	{ "question": "奢侈", "answers": [ "しゃし" ], "comment": "luxury; extravagance" },
	{ "question": "燦々", "answers": [ "さんさん" ], "comment": "brilliant; bright" },
	{ "question": "敷設", "answers": [ "ふせつ" ], "comment": "construction, laying" },
	{ "question": "槍衾", "answers": [ "やりぶすま" ], "comment": "line of spears held at the ready" },
	{ "question": "石臼", "answers": [ "いしうす" ], "comment": "stone mortar; millstone; quern" },
	{ "question": "緑青", "answers": [ "ろくしょう" ], "comment": "verdigris; green rust; copper rust" },
	{ "question": "分娩", "answers": [ "ぶんべん" ], "comment": "delivery; confinement; childbirth" },
	{ "question": "何れ", "answers": [ "いずれ" ], "comment": "which (of three or more)\nwhichever; any\nwell; now; let me see\nwhere; which; who\nanyway; anyhow; at any rate\nsooner or later; eventually; one of these days; at some future date or time\nboth; either; any; all; whichever" },
	{ "question": "息む", "answers": [ "いきむ" ], "comment": "to strain (e.g. with constipation)\nto bear or push down (during childbirth)" },
	{ "question": "惨憺", "answers": [ "さんたん" ], "comment": "miserable; pitiful; tragic; wretched; horrible" },
	{ "question": "手水鉢", "answers": [ "ちょうずばち" ], "comment": "washbasin; stoup or font for cleaning hands (esp. tea house, garden decoration, or for ablutions when visiting a shrine or temple)" },
	{ "question": "箍", "answers": [ "たが" ], "comment": "hoop; binding (e.g. of a barrel)" },
	{ "question": "引き摺る", "answers": [ "ひきずる" ], "comment": "to drag along; to pull\nto force someone along\nto prolong; to drag out\nto influence strongly; to seduce" },
	{ "question": "引き攣る", "answers": [ "ひきつる" ], "comment": "to have a cramp (spasm, convulsion, twitch); to become stiff" },
	{ "question": "暖簾", "answers": [ "のれん" ], "comment": "(short) sign curtain hung at shop entrance\nreputation (of a store); goodwill" },
	{ "question": "鳶色", "answers": [ "とびいろ" ], "comment": "reddish brown" },
	{ "question": "双眸", "answers": [ "そうぼう" ], "comment": "pair of eyes" },
	{ "question": "図体", "answers": [ "ずうたい" ], "comment": "body; frame" },
	{ "question": "猜疑", "answers": [ "さいぎ" ], "comment": "suspicion; jealousy" },
	{ "question": "暫く", "answers": [ "しばらく" ], "comment": "little while; short while; moment; instant\na while; quite a time\nit's been a long time" },
	{ "question": "蛭", "answers": [ "ひる" ], "comment": "leech" },
	{ "question": "逼迫", "answers": [ "ひっぱく" ], "comment": "stringency (financial); (monetary) tightness\nimpending (dangers); pressing (crisis)" },
	{ "question": "旱魃", "answers": [ "かんばつ" ], "comment": "drought; long spell (period) of dry weather" },
	{ "question": "御髪", "answers": [ "おぐし", "みぐし" ], "comment": "hair" },
	{ "question": "肋", "answers": [ "あばら" ], "comment": "rib; rib cage\nboned rib (esp. of pork or beef)" },
	{ "question": "肋骨", "answers": [ "あばらぼね", "ろっこつ" ], "comment": "rib\nframe (of a ship)" },
	{ "question": "頻りに", "answers": [ "しきりに" ], "comment": "frequently; repeatedly; often; incessantly; constantly\nstrongly; eagerly" },
	{ "question": "真似", "answers": [ "まね" ], "comment": "imitating; copying; mimicry\nbehavior; behaviour; action; conduct" },
	{ "question": "真似る", "answers": [ "まねる" ], "comment": "to mimic; to imitate" },
	{ "question": "出で立ち", "answers": [ "いでたち" ], "comment": "dress; outfit" },
	{ "question": "遣り通す", "answers": [ "やりとおす" ], "comment": "to carry through; to achieve; to complete" },
	{ "question": "遣る", "answers": [ "やる" ], "comment": "to do; to undertake; to perform; to play (a game); to study\nto send; to dispatch; to despatch\nto put; to move; to turn (one's head, glance, etc.)\nto give (esp. to someone of equal or lower status); to let have; to present; to bestow; to confer\nto make (a vehicle) go faster\nto run (a business); to keep; to be engaged in; to practice (law, medicine, etc.); to practise\nto have (food, drink, etc.); to eat; to drink; to smoke\nto hold (a performance); to perform; to show\nto ease (one's mind)\nto harm; to injure; to kill\nto have sex with\nto live; to get by; to get along\nto do ... completely\nto do ... broadly; to do ... to a great distance\nto do ... for (someone of equal or lower status); to do ... to (sometimes with negative nuance)\nto make active efforts to ..." },
	{ "question": "束の間", "answers": [ "つかのま" ], "comment": "moment; brief time; brief; transient" },
	{ "question": "咽ぶ", "answers": [ "むせぶ" ], "comment": "to be choked; to be stifled; to be smothered" },
	{ "question": "栄華", "answers": [ "えいが" ], "comment": "glory; splendour; splendor; majesty; luxury" },
	{ "question": "料簡", "answers": [ "りょうけん" ], "comment": "idea; thought; intention; design; inclination; decision; motive\ndiscretion\nforgiveness; toleration" },
	{ "question": "困憊", "answers": [ "こんぱい" ], "comment": "exhaustion; fatigue" },
	{ "question": "柔和", "answers": [ "にゅうわ" ], "comment": "gentle; mild; meek; tender" },
	{ "question": "拐かす", "answers": [ "かどわかす" ], "comment": "to kidnap" },
	{ "question": "敷衍", "answers": [ "ふえん" ], "comment": "expatiation; amplification (upon); elaboration" },
	{ "question": "知悉", "answers": [ "ちしつ" ], "comment": "complete knowledge" },
	{ "question": "喫緊", "answers": [ "きっきん" ], "comment": "urgent; pressing; exigent" },
	{ "question": "菩薩", "answers": [ "ぼさつ" ], "comment": "bodhisattva; one who has reached enlightenment but vows to save all beings before becoming a buddha\nHigh Monk (title bestowed by the imperial court)\ntitle bestowed to Shinto kami in manifestation theory" }
]
}
